Very nice to meet you.
Any friend of Miss Stewart's is welcome at Somsak's. Stewart
Follow me, please.
I like it here.
I do, too. I come here often.
A special place for special people.
Thank you, Somsak.
Well! Nice restaurant.
Would you like something to drink?
Yes, I'd like a glass of ginger ale with ice.
Harry, what would you like? Harry
Do you have a dry white wine?
How about a California chablis?
Chablis is fine.
What would you like to eat?
I'd like the mee krob.
Harry, would you like to see a menu? Harry
No, it's Ok.
I'll have the mee krob also.
What is it?
Crispy fried noodles. I love them.
May I bring you a salad?
Oh yes.
What do you recommend today?
I recommend rose-petal salad.
Special for new friends.
Rose-petal salad?
Why not?
I'll take care of everything.
I hope you're hungry.
What? Oh, yes. Starving. Well, I...
Well, I ...
What do you do at Universe Toy Company?
I'm the vice-president of new toy development.
Terrific!
I know you 're a CPA.
That's true. Harry Bennett,
certified public accountant.
I love numbers.
I do some work for Smith and Dale,
Your company's accounting firm.
And so...
Here we are.
Yes.
I have a daughter.
I know. How old is she?
She's nine years old.
That's a nice age. What's her name?
Michelle. Michelle
Do you have a picture of her?
She's very pretty.
Thank you.
Rose-petal salad.
And there's a phone call for you, Mr. Bennett. Bennett
Excuse me, Susan.
I hope nothing is wrong.
I'll get the rest of the dinner.
Excuse me.
Please forgive me, Susan, but...
I have to leave. I feel terrible, but...
What's the matter?
My daughter isn't feeling well.
Oh no! Is it serious?
I don't know. The baby-sitter says she has a stomachache,
and she's crying.
I'll have to go home.
Will you forgive me?
Of course. I'm so sorry for Michelle.
And you didn't have a chance to eat.
Oh, it's OK.
Let me take you home first.
No, no. Please, go ahead.
It's our first date.
We'll make another.
Please don't worry.
I'll phone you.
I hope your daughter is all right. Good-bye.
Good-bye.