Philip... Ellen.
Ah, Judge.
How are you?
I think it's time for the wedding to begin.
All right, ladies and gentlemen.
Please take your places.
The wedding ceremony is about to begin.
OK, Jane. Start the music.
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
to join this man and this woman in holy matrimony.
Do either of you have any reason
why you should not be legally joined in marriage?
Is there anyone present who can show
any just cause why these two people
should not be legally joined in marriage?
Then, Harry Bennett, do you take Susan Stewart
to be your lawful, wedded wife?
I do.
And you, Susan Stewart,
do you take Harry Bennett
to be your lawful, wedded husband?
I do.
The rings, please.
I have them, Harry.
By the power vested in me by the laws of the State of New York,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride now, Harry.