Subtitles added by Hanson Hu
root@pythoner.work
Episode 11 - A Place of Our Own
Ellen, I'd like your opinion.
About what?
Well, Richard and I feel that with a baby coming
we need to have our own place to live.
Oh.
Well, what do you think about Richard and me
looking for a small house or an apartment
at this point in our lives?
We love having you here,
and there is room,
and ... and when the baby comes,
the baby can stay in your room for a while.
Richard feels we need to find a small house.
I remember when I was pregnant with Richard.
Philip and I were living with Grandma and Grandpa.
Philip was a young doctor, Philip
and he kept talking about having a house of our own.
It's natural.
What did you do?
We looked at a lot of houses.
Did you find one?
Oh, not at first.
We couldn't afford it.
Grandpa wanted to lend us the money to buy one,
but Philip is too independent.
He didn't want to borrow any money.
Sounds like Richard.
They're all alike.
Richard is a real Stewart.
He's independent,
and sometimes just stubborn.
When did you buy a house?
After Richard was born.
I was teaching music,
and Philip was opening his first medical office.
Where was the house?
Right here in Riverdale.
Of course, it was a small house,
but just right for us.
It's funny. History repeats itself.
Now Richard and I are having a baby,
and we probably won't be able to
afford a house right away, either.
Why don't you look at some houses, Marilyn?
Good idea.
Look in the real-estate section of Sunday's Times.
You'll learn a lot.
Maybe we should
speak to a real-estate agent about a house.
And a bank about a mortgage.
I'll talk to Richard about it.
I think it's a good idea, Ellen.
We can learn a lot by asking.
And if I can be of any help,
let me know.
As a matter of fact,
my friend Virginia Martinelli is a real-estate agent.
Good.
You won't believe this,
but she sold us our first house and this one.
Well, I'll tell Richard,
and we'll go to see her.
Do you think the skirt length is right, Ellen?
Do you think it's too long?
I think the skirt is just right.
Are you planning to attach a train to it?
No. No train. Just the dress.
But I am going to make a headpiece of lace.
That dress is gorgeous.
Thanks, Ellen.
And thanks for the advice about the house.
I'll talk to Richard about it
the minute he comes home.
And remember,
we love having you here.
There's no need to rush.
I remember your parents' first house very well.
It was on Spring Avenue, near the park.
I grew up in that house.
Yes, and you were such a cute baby.
I've seen pictures of him.
He had blond hair.
I've been friendly with the Stewart family
for a long time,
so it's my pleasure
to help you find a house now.
Well, we're not sure we can afford one.
But we'd like to find out
about the possibilities.
That's a good idea.
I love your house on Linden Street.
I sold your father that house seventeen years ago.
Really?
Yes, Mom was pregnant with Robbie then,
and they needed the extra room.
I hear you're expecting a baby, Mrs. Stewart.
Mmm-hmm.
So we will be needing more room.
Oh, so you don't need something immediately?
No. But in five or six months...
And time passes so quickly.
Yes, it does.
Well, when you called,
you gave me enough information
about your salaries and your savings.
So I have a good idea about your financial situation.
Let me show you some pictures of houses.
With two bedrooms?
Yes, I think I can show you some.
Of course, they won't be in Riverdale.
The cost of housing's too high for you here.
I haven't thought about living anywhere else.
We've always lived in this area.
Where should we look for a house, Mrs. Martinelli?
Well, we have an office in Mount Kisco.
It's a lovely area,
and it's only about an hour's drive from here.
Here.
I have a book with photos of some homes in that area.
Now, let's see.
Here
This is a lovely two-bedroom house in your price range.
It's pretty,
but I prefer a two-story home.
I do, too.
I don't care for a ranch type.
OK.
Oh, this is a wonderful house.
I know it well.
I sold it to the present owners.
It looks wonderful.
This is a two-bedroom, two-bath house.
It has a full basement,
and it is on a half-acre lot.
You can probably afford this one.
I like this house.
So do I.
And the price is right.
Would you like to go see it?
Yes. We're planning
to talk to someone at the bank next week.
Perhaps we could see the house this weekend.
If someone doesn't buy it before then,
But let's keep looking.
Just to get an idea of some other possibilities.
This is very helpful, Mrs. Martinelli.
Here.
This is a wonderful example of Spanish-style architecture.
I love the roof tiles on a Spanish-style house.
It looks like the houses in Hollywood.
It's interesting.
A house like this in Riverdale costs double the price.
Oh my!
Here's a real buy.
It's a bargain.
This house just came on the market.
It's quite lovely.
Is it a two-bedroom house?
No. It has three bedrooms and three baths.
I know the house.
It has a brand new kitchen.
And a living room with a twelve-foot ceiling.
And there's a two-car garage.
Then why don't we go look at this house, too?
It's a good investment.
Thank you, Mrs. Martinelli.
Thanks so much.
My pleasure.
Give my best to your parents.
Your father's a wonderful doctor, Richard.
He took care of my daughter
when she was a child.
He's the best pediatrician in Westchester.
Thanks, Mrs. Martinelli.
I'll give them your regards.
We really appreciate your advice.
I do think you should go see the houses
and talk to the bank.
Here.
Let me give you some information sheets about the houses.
They're both very good buys.
Well, thanks so much for your help and your time,
Mrs. Martinelli.
We've got a lot to talk about.
Mmm-hmm. Thanks.
How do you do?
Hello.
I'm Ralph Riley.
I'm Richard Stewart, and this is my wife, Marilyn.
Pleased to meet you.
Likewise, Mr. Riley.
Please, sit down. What can I do for you?
We'd like to discuss a mortgage.
For a house.
Fine. Are you buying a house
or are you refinancing your present home?
We're planning to buy a house.
And we'd like to find out about a mortgage.
We are customers of the bank.
As a matter of fact, my whole family banks here.
I have some questions to ask.
Do you own your house or do you rent?
Neither.
We live with my parents, Dr. and Mrs. Philip Stewart.
And how old are you?
I'm twenty-nine.
I'm thirty.
And, Mr. Stewart, what is your occupation?
I'm a freelance photographer.
And, Mrs. Stewart, are you working?
Yes. I'm a designer, and I work in a boutique.
Did you bring any savings or salary information?
Last year's tax forms?
Yes. Here they are.
OK. What... what kind of house did you have in mind?
We're talking about buying
a two-bedroom house in Mount Kisco.
Here are the financial details on the house.
Thank you.
Are you prepared to make a ten-percent down payment?
Yes, we are.
Payments over thirty years?
Yes.
Do you think we can get a loan?
Well, it depends. Do you own any other property?
Any stocks or bonds?
No.
I see. Then you don't have any collateral.
Perhaps you could get a guarantor -
someone to sign for the loan for you.
Why is that necessary?
Since you don't have enough income,
and you don't already own any property,
the bank needs to be sure
you can pay the mortgage every month.
A guarantor is responsible for the loan
if you can't make the payments.
I see. Well, the idea of buying a house is exciting.
Thank you, Mr. Riley. We'll read this over carefully.
Thank you.
Good-bye. Thanks.
Good-bye. And hope to see you soon.
I hope so, too.
Take care.
Good-bye.
It all sounded so easy
until they mentioned needing collateral or a guarantor.
We have no collateral.
And I don't think it's a good idea
to ask Dad to sign as a guarantor.
I don't feel right about it.
I understand your feelings about it, Richard.
Now, tell me, what's the problem?
We can get a loan from the bank
if we can put up some collateral.
And we don't own anything to use as collateral.
Or someone can sign with us as a guarantor.
Why don't you speak to Dad?
No. If we buy a house, I want to be able to handle it alone.
Everybody needs help sometimes, Richard.
I understand Richard's feelings about it, Ellen.
In two or three months, I'll have an advance on my book
and be able to put more money down.
What about the house in Mount Kisco?
Somebody else'll buy it by then.
Then there'll be other houses, Marilyn.
Richard has a point. You're just beginning to look.
We're in no great rush. It's true.
This has been a great learning experience for us, Marilyn.
Talking to the real-estate agent.
Looking at the houses.
Talking to the loan officer at the bank.
It has been a learning experience. That's true.
I think you're doing the right thing. Taking your time.
Looking around. Especially with a purchase of this kind.
You're talking about a lot of money.
We'll call Mrs. Martinelli and tell her to keep looking for us.
And I'll call Mr. Riley at the bank
and tell him we'll see him in a couple of months.
And if you ever need Dad or me to help you ...
We know.
You know we'll be there for you.
It's a Stewart tradition. We're a family.