Subtitles added by Hanson Hu
root@pythoner.work
Episode 16 - Full of Surprises
The mailman just dropped some mail in our box, Grandpa.
Probably a lot of advertising and bills.
Why don't you write to me, Robbie,
so I can get some interesting mail?
You were right, Grandpa.
Advertising, bills, bills, advertising.
Yes. It's just like I said, Robbie.
Nothing interesting.
You won't believe it, Grandpa,
but there's a letter here addressed to you,
Mr. Malcolm Stewart, and it looks like a personal letter.
Oh, it must be a bill.
I don't think so.
The return name and address is
Pete Waters, RFD Number 1, Chesterton.
You're joking. Pete Waters?
You know him?
Do I know Pete Waters?
You bet I do!
He was my roommate in college.
He visited with Grandma and me in Florida
about five years ago.
What does he say?
Is he OK?
Yeah, he's fine.
Just fine.
He's writing to invite me
to spend a weekend with him at his farm.
He's planning a get-together
with two or three other college friends.
A kind of a fifty-year anniversary reunion.
Sounds like fun.
Fifty years? Wow!
It sounds like fun to me, too, Robbie.
What kind of farm does he have?
I've never been there, Robbie,
but he has chickens and cows and all.
That means fresh eggs and fresh milk.
Does he have a family?
No, he doesn't, Robbie.
He never married.
He's not as lucky as I am
to have a family and grandchildren.
I'm a lucky man.
How come he never got married?
That's a good question, Robbie.
A very good question.
He never married because
the girl he was in love with in college married someone else.
As simple as that.
He never got over it.
He must have loved her very much.
Yes. Very much.
Lillian Winters.
She was in our class.
And what happened?
She was in love with Donald McGrath,
the quarterback on our football team.
Football players are always popular with the ladies.
She liked Pete, and they went to dances together.
But her heart was with Donald.
Did he ever get over it?
No, he never did.
Where is she today?
I don't know.
Maybe Lillian will be at the reunion.
You think so?
Pete's full of surprises.
I wish I could go there with you, Grandpa.
What do you think the surprise will be?
With Pete, you never know, Robbie.
Won't it be exciting to see all your college friends there again?
It is already.
I'm kind of excited about going now.
Next weekend...
sleep over Friday and Saturday night
and come back Sunday.
I can't wait!
Don't you think you ought to call Pete
and tell him you're coming?
You're reading my mind, Robbie.
Hello. What can I do for you?
Hi. Fill 'er up.
I need a full tank.
Check the hood?
No, thanks.
Whereabouts are you headed?
Pete Waters's farm, near Chesterton.
I know it well.
Pete Waters's lived around here almost as long as I have.
How long is it going to take for me to get there?
About fifteen minutes.
There's a shortcut - if you know it.
No, I don't.
Could you tell me how to use the shortcut?
Sure. You take the next left turn.
You'll see a stop sign.
Make a right at the stop sign.
Stay on that road, and you'll cross a blue bridge.
Then you'll see a big old red barn.
That's the back of Pete Waters's place.
That's quite a difference from the directions that Pete sent me.
Now, if you take that route, it's probably a lot simpler,
but it'll take you ten minutes longer.
OK. Let me repeat it.
I take the next left turn to the stop sign.
Then a right across a blue bridge,
and then a big red barn.
Can't miss it.
How much do I owe you?
Well, that'll be eighteen dollars and seventy cents.
No charge for the cleanup.
It's on the house.
Well, here's a twenty.
Ah. OK. That's a dollar and thirty cents change.
There we go... will make twenty. Thanks.
Thank you.
And thanks for the directions.
This must be Pete's barn.
Turn right to the house.
Hi.
Hi. What can I do for you?
Is this the Pete Waters farm?
It is.
I'm a friend of Pete's.
I'm looking for the house.
It's just over yonder.
Keep along this road
till you get to the end of the fence.
You'll see the chicken house.
His house is on the left.
Well, thanks.
"Have gone to the railroad station.
Back soon with a surprise.
Make yourself at home.
Have a look around. Pete."
Same old Pete Waters.
Always full of surprises.
Don't tell me.
Please don't tell me.
I recognize you...
Oh, don't be silly, Arnie.
Of course you recognize him.
Except for the beard, he hasn't changed in fifty years.
It's Malcolm Stewart!
I know it's Malcolm Stewart.
You haven't changed much in fifty years.
Peggy... Peggy Pendleton!
You're Peggy Pendleton!
Who am I, you old rascal?
You don't recognize me, do you?
I know who you are.
You're Arnold Franklin!
I know who you are!
You look wonderful, Malcolm!
Sit down. Sit down.
Pete isn't home. Pete
Really?
No. He left a note on the door
saying he was going to the railroad station
to pick up a surprise.
He's so funny.
Always full of surprises,
even fifty years later.
The two of you look unbelievable!
How's your family?
Oh, I was sorry
to hear about your wife having passed away.
Yes. About four years ago.
And you're living with your children now? In New York?
Pete wrote us and told us.
Yup.
Retired and moved to New York
to live with my son and his family.
By the way,
what do you think this big surprise is?
It could be most anything, knowing Pete.
Hey, that must be Pete!
Now we'll find out about the surprise.
So good to see you all!
Oh, Pete, Pete!
Oh, it's so good to see you!
Remember Lillian?
I remember all of you.
You haven't changed a bit.
Lillian! Oh, my gosh!
Lillian Winters.
We were together in the Thursday night drama society.
Remember me, Malcolm?
Oh, beautiful as ever, Lillian.
How's Donald?
That's OK, Malcolm.
Donald passed away a couple of years ago.
Sorry to hear that, Lillian.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I would not have missed this get-together for the world!
And your little surprise, Pete?
You really surprised me
by having us all come together.
You don't know what the surprise is yet?
Come on!
We'll tell you the big surprise.
I've invited you here for the weekend to help celebrate.
Celebrate?
Our fiftieth reunion?
No.
No. Pete wants to tell you ...
Now, let me have the honor, Lillian.
For goodness' sake, Pete, tell us!
I can't wait much longer.
Well, I am pouring this iced tea
so that we can toast Lillian and me.
You don't mean to tell me that you and...
Yes, I do.
I have loved Lillian all these years,
so I asked her to be Mrs. Pete Waters.
And I said yes.
I knew it! I knew it!
Congratulations!
Oh, Lillian,
I am so happy for you both.
It's wonderful!
It's wonderful for me.
Lillian will make me a happy man, finally.
You are full of surprises, Pete.
We are going to
spend the entire weekend having a good time together here
on the farm.
We are going to celebrate all weekend.
When is the wedding?
That's another surprise.
Lillian and I were married two weeks ago in Detroit.
She's come here to stay.
Wait till I tell my family about this!
Why, that's wonderful!