Subtitles added by Hanson Hu
root@pythoner.work
Episode 17 - Photo Finish
What are you doing?
I think I've got them.
You think you've got what?
Performing arts... performing arts centers.
I think I've got them all, but I'm not sure.
I think you have got it, Richard.
Lincoln Center, home of the Metropolitan Opera,
the New York City Ballet, the New York Philharmonic.
Shubert Alley, center of the theater on Broadway.
And Carnegie Hall.
And the Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts in Washington.
And the Music Center in Los Angeles.
And the others. I do have it all.
You have been working on this for some time, Richard.
I'm glad you feel you've finally put it all together.
What now?
Now for the hard part.
Oh, you think you're going to have a hard time
getting the album published?
Well, it won't be easy.
So, what do you think you're going to do?
Does the name Harvey Carlson ring a bell?
Oh, yes! Harvey Carlson! I remember.
He said I should call him.
He's the publisher of the Carlson Publishing Company.
He said they need a new book of photographs,
and he really liked my concept.
So, why don't you call him in the morning?
Do you think I have enough to show him?
I've been through every section with you, Richard.
It's quite complete.
And now that you're satisfied with the performing arts section,
I think you should show it to Mr. Carlson.
You're right. My Family Album, U.S.A. feels right.
I'll call in the morning and set up an appointment to see him.
He's going to love your work.
Come on. Let's get some sleep.
Is it too early to call Mr. Carlson?
Seven after nine? No. I'm sure he's in his office.
His number is five, five, five, seven, five, three, two.
Five, five, five, seven, five, three, two.
Hello. Mr. Carlson, please.
Mr. Carlson is busy at the moment. May I help you?
I'd like to make an appointment with him.
And your name is...?
My name is Richard Stewart.
He told me to call him about my project,
Family Album, U.S.A.
One moment, please.
What's going on?
I guess they're trying to set up an appointment for me.
Mr. Stewart, I just spoke to Mr. Carlson. Stewart.
He would like to see you.
But the only time he's available this week
is tomorrow morning at ten o'clock.
Thanks. Thanks a lot. Good-bye.
Well, it's done. Tomorrow morning at a publisher's office.
Oh, it's so exciting, isn't it, Richard?
Well, finally a publisher will see my work.
Good morning.
Good morning. My name is Richard Stewart.
I'm here to see Mr. Carlson.
Please sit down, Mr. Stewart.
Mr. Carlson will be with you shortly.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Mr. Carlson,
but Richard Stewart is here
for his ten o'clock appointment with you.
OK. Thank you.
Like I said, he'll be with you shortly.
Thank you.
Yes, Mr. Carlson. Yes, sir.
He's ready for you, Mr. Stewart.
Thank you. In there?
Yes. In there. Good luck.
Come in, come in.
This is a crazy morning. Hello, Richard.
Hello, Mr. Carlson.
Sit down, sit down.
Thank you for seeing me on such short notice.
I hope you've brought your pictures along.
I see that you have. Let's get right to it.
We need a new coffee-table book,
and a book of photos about the United States still feels right.
OK, let's take a look.
Good. Very good. Family Album, U.S.A.
It's an excellent title.
If you had to describe the book in one sentence,
how would you do it?
Well, I'd describe it as a book which is a...
a portrait of the United States -
the places, the people, mostly the people.
The things they do, the ways they live,
the places they visit, and the landmarks.
A photographic journey.
These are wonderful.
These photos in your performing arts section.
Carnegie Hall, Lincoln Center.
I'm glad you like them.
I do, but...
But?
There's something missing. You've got a good eye, Richard.
You're a terrific photographer.
But before I can publish your work,
I need to meet with my marketing department,
and you've got to do one more thing.
What's that, Mr. Carlson?
In the section on culture,
you've included performing arts centers,
but you've left out street performance.
The mimes.
Richard, if you go out
and photograph street performances in the city,
you'll have it.
That is a great idea.
The performing arts centers and the street performances.
I'll do it.
If you do it, I'll publish your work.
Are you serious?
I've never been more serious.
When do you think you can return with street performances?
A couple of weeks.
If they're as good as the rest of these pictures, it's a deal.
You won't be disappointed, Mr. Carlson. Thanks.
Good-bye, Richard, and good luck. See you in two weeks.
Good-bye, Mr. Carlson. Thanks.
So if you like the street-performance photos,
you'll really publish Family Album, U.S.A.?
When I say something, I mean it.
Go to work. Good-bye.
Good-bye.
Two weeks. I said I could do it in two weeks, and I did it.
The pictures you've taken are fabulous, Richard.
Mr. Carlson will love them.
Monday morning.
I'm going to show him the photos on Monday morning.
I can't wait!
I'm very proud of you. You really did a beautiful job.
I know he will love the new photographs for your book.
Yeah. I really did do a good job, didn't I?
Hey, you know? There's still some film left on this roll,
and there's one person I haven't photographed in a long time.
Who?
You.
Richard! I haven't brushed my hair.
You look great!
It's not fair, Richard. I'm not even ready.
Oh, that's wonderful! That's wonderful!
Wonderful!
Thanks.
Fabulous!
Terrific!
Thanks.
They get better and better.
Thanks a lot.
This is sensational!
Yeah. Thanks.
What a job! Good work, Richard!
I'm so glad you like them so much.
Like them? They represent your best work.
Really?
Absolutely.
Well... what do you think? Do I have my book?
You do. You do. There's a book here.
I'll have a contract
and an advance payment waiting for you
first thing in the morning.
Thank you.
And while you're here,
I would like to introduce you to your editor.
And I want you to meet the people in the art department.
I'll set up an appointment with the marketing people.
When do you think we'll be through?
In about half an hour. Why?
I can't wait to tell Marilyn!