Subtitles added by Hanson Hu
root@pythoner.work
Episode 25 - Country Music
Hot dogs. I love hot dogs.
There is nothing better than a hot dog in the country.
Hot dogs and mustard.
Cooked outdoors over an open fire.
I wish I had one now.
Do you remember when Daddy and I used to take you
and Susan and Robbie to Jones Beach?
Oh, I sure do.
We'd wait until dark and make a fire,
and we'd cook the hot dogs.
Oh, don't forget the mustard.
And, oh, does anybody want ketchup?
I might as well take it along.
And now to make sure we've got the hamburger patties.
I have to remember to put them in the bag
tomorrow morning before we leave.
I'll remind you, Richard.
Mom,
we really appreciate your taking care of Max for the weekend
and giving up your free time.
I love doing it.
Susan and Harry have a sitter for Michelle in the city,
and I'm taking care of Max.
It's no big deal.
I am happy to do it for you.
I guess Max is asleep by now.
He's not crying anymore.
Oh, poor baby. He's teething.
Well, he's asleep, finally.
I feel so bad for him.
It hurts so much when a baby gets his first teeth.
He'll be fine, Marilyn.
Well, he wakes up several times during the night,
and the pain is so bad.
I'm really concerned about going away for the weekend, Ellen,
and leaving you with the full responsibility of taking care of Max.
Especially with his teething.
I wish he felt better.
Please don't worry, Marilyn.
Remember your father-in-law's a pediatrician.
We have a live-in doctor if there's a problem I can't handle.
I agree, Marilyn.
We really don't have to be overly concerned.
I'll go upstairs and stay with him until he falls asleep again.
Thanks, Richard.
Try putting him across your lap on his stomach.
He likes that.
I'll try it.
When are Susan and Harry picking you up, Marilyn?
They're coming by at six tomorrow morning,
so we can get an early start.
That's nice.
And you'll have a full day in the country.
And a full night.
Tomorrow night we'll be camping out in tents.
And coming home on Sunday?
We'll be heading back late in the afternoon.
You're going to have the time of your lives.
Camping out is such great fun.
We'll have a great time camping out, I'm sure.
But I'm still a little worried about you, Ellen.
It will be my great pleasure, Marilyn.
Remember, it's only one night.
He's asleep.
I think he'll sleep through the night now.
Thanks, honey.
I hope he's good when we're away.
Well, so do I.
Now, to check the list of things we need for the camping trip.
We need to bring a flashlight.
It's in the right-hand drawer, next to the bottle openers.
Do we have a bottle opener on the list, Marilyn?
No. No bottle opener.
Is that one of the things Susan and Harry are bringing?
No.
And we're bringing the ketchup, mustard, relish, all that stuff.
And cooking utensils.
Well, here's the bottle opener, and here's the flashlight.
Matches.
Yes, of course.
For when we build our campfire.
I can't build a fire by rubbing two pieces of wood together.
And don't forget your camera and film, Richard.
All packed and ready.
And let's not forget our cassette player and some tapes.
Some music tapes and some blank tapes
so that we can record our thoughts about the trip.
Oh, that's a nice idea.
An audio diary.
That's what I thought.
Got it!
The cassette player and the tapes.
Oh, I love it!
I love it!
To be away from the city on such a beautiful day
is my idea of heaven!
The grass. The trees. The fresh air.
I told you you'd like it. I've been doing this for years.
You have the spirit of a teenager, Susan.
Wait till you see yourself jumping around.
That's what I love about Susan.
She works hard.
She plays hard.
She's a real Stewart.
Come on, Richard.
Help me get this stuff out of the car.
Where does it go?
Well, we'll put everything over there.
We'll set up our tents over there by the edge of the woods.
Then we'll be able to make our fire there where it's safe.
Oh, there's our table and benches.
All set for eating.
That's what makes this spot so good.
Is anybody hungry?
I am.
We just got here.
When you're out in the fresh air like this, it makes you hungry.
Aren't you hungry, Marilyn?
I sure am.
How about you, Richard?
Starving.
You guys are like three kids.
Aren't you hungry, Harry?
Well, yeah.
Now that you mention it, I guess I am.
I mean,
how could a guy not be hungry with all this talk about eating?
Where's the bag with the chicken salad sandwiches?
Right here, next to the ice packs. Here.
Put the tablecloth on the picnic table,
and I will bring the cola and the plastic cups.
Well, how do you like it so far?
I've never been more relaxed.
Me, neither.
I wish we had brought Michelle, Harry.
She would have loved it.
Oh, you're right.
I wish we had brought Max.
Marilyn, Susan, let's not begin to worry about Michelle and Max.
We're having a good time, and they're in good hands.
Richard is right.
Are you having a good time, Susan?
You haven't answered my question.
I am having a good time, Harry.
I promise not to think about the city.
We're in the country.
Let's all just enjoy this wonderful place
and this wonderful weather.
Good.
This is heaven, Harry!
It was such a great idea to spend the weekend this way.
Thanks, Susan.
I thought you'd all like it.
Like it?
Listen to the sounds of the summer that surround us.
It's so calming.
I've always liked camping out.
Away from the telephones and account books.
It's refreshing for me.
I always go back to the city in a wonderful state of mind.
We've only been here for a day,
and I've completely forgotten about all my business problems.
The office seems so far away.
I'm glad you like it, Susan.
We'll spend many more weekends like this.
And next time we'll bring Michelle.
I wish she were here with us to enjoy the country.
Just listen to the sound.
It's so soothing.
I can hardly keep my eyes open.
If only we could bottle the fresh air.
Wouldn't it be wonderful?
We could call it "Deep Sleep Country Air."
It puts you to sleep.
So does the sound.
I've been having a hard time keeping my eyes open
just listening to it.
It's like a special music.
Too bad we can't bottle the sound.
But we can!
Can what?
Bottle the sound.
What are you talking about?
Oh, yeah?
Great idea!
Let's do it!
I'm so glad everyone is asleep.
I thought Max would be crying, and everybody would be awake.
What did I tell you?
Nothing to worry about.
I'm sure everything is fine.
My mother knows all there is to know
about taking care of babies, I assure you.
Let's put some of this stuff away and then take off.
We've got a forty-minute drive into the city.
Welcome home,
and I do mean welcome home.
Something wrong?
Oh, nothing's wrong, Richard.
Believe me, Max is fine.
But his teeth hurt, and he just can't get to sleep, poor dear.
Neither can you.
Oh, I feel so bad.
Oh, I'm fine.
How was your weekend?
We had a great time, Mom.
It was wonderful.
The weather couldn't have been better.
It was nice here, too.
Did you get a chance to get outside at all?
Oh, yes.
Grandpa helped me yesterday afternoon.
I went to the supermarket to get a few things,
and I stayed out an extra half hour.
The village was filled with people. The weather was so nice.
Harry's a professional camper, Mom.
He knows all there is to know,
and he made the weekend very easy for us to enjoy.
Come on. You all helped.
You were wonderful, Harry!
Why don't you go to your room, Mom, and get some sleep.
Oh, I'm fine.
Tell me more about your weekend.
Did you do anything special?
Lots of special country things.
We picked flowers.
And we brought some home for you.
It was so nice to be out in the country.
They smell wonderful.
Everything smelled so special.
It would have been great if we had been able to bottle the smells.
It would be a great business if you could do that.
Oh!
Uh, we're home now, Ellen.
We'll take care of it.
I'll take care of it.
Let's see if it works.
What's that?
A little special country music.
I think we'd better head home.
It's getting late, and we have a bit of a drive.
Well, all your things are inside.
There's your sleeping bag.
Oh, thanks, Harry.
Say good-bye to Richard.
We'll call you all tomorrow night.
Good-bye.
Bye, Mom.
I'm so tired I think I'm overtired.
I don't know if I can get to sleep.
Max has stopped crying.
Yes. It works!
It works!
What works?
This.
Oh. Oh, where did you get that?
It sounds so nice.
I think I'm falling asleep.
Like Max did.
Good night.
Sounds of the country.
The soothing sounds of the country.