宋涛涛 songty  taotaosong@163.com QQ:498783048
You should take the number 1 subway. 应当搭一路地铁。
Is there a station near here? 附近有地铁站吗
Yes. The station's that way. 有。地铁站在那边。
You should take the number 1 train to Van Cortlandt Park. 到Van Cortlandt公园 下车。搭一路车
Number 1 train to Van Cortlandt Park. Thank you. 一路车到Van Cortlaandt公园。谢谢。
Anytime. Good luck. 不用谢。祝 好运。
Remember, the number 1 train. The uptown platform. 记住 搭一路车 在在北 月
Thank you. 谢谢。宋涛涛 songty  taotaosong@163.com QQ:498783048
You're welcome. 不客气。
Is this pink too bright for me? 我穿粉红色会不会太太过 恃蘖
Mmm-hmm. It is a very bright pink. 是的 这种粉红是亮亮了点
Try this. It's size eight. 试试这一件。尺码是是八号
But I wear size ten. 但我穿十号的衣服。
How about green? It's size ten. 绿的怎麽样 它是十号的
Let me try it on. 让我试试看。
I'm taking too much of your time. 我耽误了 很多时间
It's six o'clock. 已经六点了。
Where's my husband? 我丈夫怎麽还没来
I was expecting him here at five forty-five. 我们约好了五点四十五在这会面的
Don't worry. The traffic is very heavy at this hour. 别担心。这个时间交通很糟
I know. But we're going to be late for dinner. 我知道。但我们晚餐可要迟到了
I'll take this green sweater. 我买这件绿毛衫吧
I like the color on me, don't you? 我觉得这种颜色较适合我 说
I think it looks terrific on you. 我觉得 穿上它好极了
I'm sorry I'm so late. 对不起 我迟到了这麽久
I had a really bad day. 今天真是糟透了。
It's ten after six. We're late. 现在是六点十分。我我们迟了
Robbie's cooking tonight, and dinner's at six thirty. 今晚Robbie做饭晚餐六点半开始
I know. I know. I'm really sorry. 我知道 我知道。真真的很抱歉
I left my bag of film on the ferry. 我把装底片的旅行袋袋遗放在渡船上
I went back for it, but the ferry was gone. 等我回去找的时候 船已经开走了。
I lost a whole day's work. 我丢掉一整天的工作成果
I'll call the Staten Island Ferry lost-and-found office. 我来打电话给Staten 渡轮的失物招领处。
I didn't think of that. Thanks. 我倒没有想到这个法法子。谢了
Hello. 喂 宋涛涛 songty  taotaosong@163.com QQ:498783048
Yes. The number, please, 我想问一下
of the Staten Island Ferry lost-and-found office. Staten 渡轮失物招招领处的电话号
Five five five...zero eight zero eight. 555-
Thank you. 谢谢。宋涛涛 songty  taotaosong@163.com QQ:498783048
I really appreciate it, Marilyn. 真的很感谢 Marilyn。
Hello. 喂 宋涛涛 songty  taotaosong@163.com QQ:498783048
Did anyone find a camera bag this afternoon, 请问今天下午有人捡捡到一个照相机旅行袋
a small canvas bag, 一个小的粗帆布袋
on the J. F. Kennedy Ferry?...No? 是在J. F. Kennedy汉 渡船上丢的。……没有吗
Maybe someone will find it. 也许会有人发现的。
The name is Stewart, Richard Stewart. 失主是Stewart Richard Stewart。
And the telephone number is five five five... 电话是555-
three oh nine oh. Thank you.
Sorry, Richard. They don't have it. 对不起 Richard 那没有。
Thanks, anyway. 不管怎样 我都得谢谢
There was a girl on the ferry. 在渡船上有一个女孩
Now maybe... 也许现在……
Tell me about it on the way home. 在回家的路上告诉我吧