OK, everybody. 好啦 各位。
I want to welcome Harry and his daughter Michelle 我想对Harry和他排鵐ichelle
to Thanksgiving with us. 来参加我们的感恩恩节晚餐表示欢迎
Thank you, Dr. Stewart. 谢谢你 Stewart创 夫。
Call me Philip. 叫我Philip。
OK. 好的。
But first, I think we should take a moment 不过首先 我想我我们应该用一两分
and remember the meaning of Thanksgiving. 来追忆一下感恩节节的意义
Philip, I took Michelle to a school play Philip 我带Michhelle看过学校 演出的
about the first Thanksgiving. 第一次感恩节历史史剧
Well, why don't you tell us about that, Michelle? 那好 能否给我我们讲一讲 Michell
Thanksgiving was about the Pilgrims, 感恩节是关於清教教徒
the first settlers in America. 他们是第一批来美美国定居的移民
They shared the first harvest with the Indians 他们与印第安人分分享首次收
and gave thanks. 感恩。
All right. 很正确。
Then in that spirit let each of us give thanks. 现在 本著同样心心意 让我们开始感恩
Each in his own way. 每个人用自己的方方式来表达
Who wants to begin? 谁先开始
I will. 我来。
I give thanks for being here with my family and for being well, 我感谢能在这 和和家人同住 且很健
so I can enjoy you all. 让我享受到你们大大家的温馨
All rihgt! 太好了
We love you, Grandpa. 我们爱你 爷爷。
I'd like to give thanks for a healthy year, a good job, 我感谢这一年来身身体健康 工作顺
and for meeting Harry and Michelle. 认识了Harry和Micchelle。
We'd like to give thanks for meeting Susan 我们要感谢认识了了Susa
and the Stewart family. 和Stewart一家人
I love you, Daddy. 我爱你 爸爸。
Thanks, Harry. 谢谢你 Harry。
That was very kind of you. 你真周到。
I'd like to give thanks for Grandpa coming to live with us. 我感谢爷爷到这 和我们一起生活。
And I'd also like to thank my math teacher 我还要感谢我的数数学老
for giving me a passing grade. 给我及格分数。
And call me, Alexandra. 还有 打电话给我我 Alexandra
Oh, Robbie! 啊 Robbie
She'll call. 她会打的。
You go first, Marilyn. 先讲 Marilyn
I'm thinking. 我还在想。
You go first. 你先来。
Well, you all know I'm working on my photo album. 好吧 你们都知道道我正在进行我的写真集
It's not finished yet. 现在还没有完成。
And I'd like to thank Marilyn for being so patient. 我要感谢Marilyn父冻龅哪托摹
Thanks, Richard. 谢谢你 Richard
I should thank you for encouraging me 我应该感谢你一直直鼓励
to keep working on my fashion designs. 继续我的服装设计计工作
I'm lucky to have a husband with an artistic eye. 我很庆幸 我丈夫夫具有艺术的眼光
Oh, we have a lot to be thankful for. 啊 我们有很多需需要感谢的事情
For the food on this table. 感谢这桌上的丰盛盛食物
Just like the Pilgrims. 就像早年清教徒那那样
I'll go along with that, Ellen. 我也有同感 Elleen。
Well, help me serve, Robbie. 好 帮我分菜 Roobbie。
It was a wonderful meal, Mrs. Stewart. 真是一顿精美的晚晚餐 Stewart太太
Thank you. 谢谢 。
And now to see the end of the football game. 现在去看看足球赛赛的最後一段
Exactly. 正合我意。
Where are you going, Philip? 你上哪去 Philip
Remember, the Michigan football game? 记得吗 Michigann足球赛
And Michigan needs a touchdown. Michigan队需要达达阵得分
Did you forget something? 你是否忘了什麽东东
Dad, your famous apple pie. 爸爸 你最著名的的苹果派
Just let me see the score, Ellen. 让我去看看比数 Ellen。
Go ahead, Philip. 去吧 Philip。
We should all take a little break before dessert. 吃甜点之前我们大大家应该稍微休息一下
Oh, who could that be? 啊 这会是谁呢
Oh, it must be Alexandra. 一定是Alexandra
I invited her to come by for dessert. 我邀请她来吃甜点点
You did? 请了她
I like Ellen. 我喜欢Ellen。
You know everyone, Alexandra. 你认识每一位吧 Alexandra。
No, she doesn't know Harry Bennett and his daughter Michelle. 不 她不认识Harrry Bennett和他女儿Michelle。
Nice to meet you. 幸会。
Hi. 好。
Hello, Alexandra. 好 Alexandra
Hi, Marilyn. 嗨 Marilyn。
Hi, Susan. 嗨 Susan。
Happy Thanksgiving. 感恩节快乐。
And Alexandra brought us a pumpkin pie. Alexandra给我们创 来了一个南瓜派。
Please sit down, Alexandra. 请坐 Alexandra
Dad, Richard--Alexandra's here. 爸爸 Richard AAlexandra来了。
Michigan needs a touchdown. Michigan队需要一一次达阵得分
Three minutes to play. 还剩三分钟。
Hi, Alexandra. Welcome. 嗨 Alexandra。换队 。
Hello, Alexandra. 好 Alexandra
Yes, Michigan needs a touchdown. 是啊 Michigan队队需要一次达阵得分
One tiny little touchdown, with just three minutes to play. 一次小小的达阵得得分 只剩下三分钟了
You want Michigan to win. 你希望Michigan队队赢球
How'd you guess? 怎麽晓得
And Alexandra brought us a pumpkin pie. Alexandra给我们创 来了一个南瓜派。
What happened? 怎麽啦
We forgot to turn the oven on. 我们忘了开烤箱开开关
We did? 我们忘了吗
Philip, why don't you go Philip 你何不去
watch the last three minutes of the game. 看完那最後三分钟钟的球赛
I will serve coffee and pumpkin pie. 我来准备咖啡和南南 吓伞
OK. I'll be back in a few minutes. 好 过几分钟我就就回来
Robbie, would you bring the dessert plates. Robbie 你把甜点点盘子拿来好
And, Marilyn, would you pour coffee, please. Marilyn请 倒一舷 咖啡。
Sure, Ellen. 当然 Ellen。
How was your Thanksgiving dinner, Alexandra? 的感恩节晚餐怎怎麽样 Alexandr
Just wonderful, Mr. Stewart. 好极了 Stewart舷 生。
The Molinas are a large family. Molina家是一个大大家族
I love being with them. 我喜欢和他们在一一起
I'm glad you came by, Alexandra. 我很高兴 来 Allexandra。
I am, too. 我也一样。
Touchdown! Touchdown! Touchdown! 达阵得分 达阵得得分 达阵得
Great Thanksgiving. 美好的感恩节。
Lots to be thankful for. 要感谢的事很多。
Michigan scored a touchdown. Michigan队达阵得得分
Alexandra came by. Alexandra来了。
And nobody misses Philip's famous apple pie. 还有 没人再想到到Philip著名的苹果派
Oh, Grandpa! 啊 爷爷