Hi, Michelle. 嗨 Michelle。
Hello, Harry. 你好 Harry。
It's nice to see you again. 很高兴再见到你们。
Hello. 好。
Hi, Susan. 嗨 Susan。
We have both been excited about seeing you 我们两个很高兴见到
and having lunch with you today. 与 一起吃中餐
Michelle picked these flowers out for you. Michelle选这些花送 。
Daddy, can we go soon? 爸爸 我们能快点走吗
We're going to go to lunch in a few minutes, honey. 我们一下子就去吃中餐餐 亲爱的
But I'm thirsty. 可是我渴了。
OK. You go out and get a drink of water at the fountain. 好。 出去在饮水机那那儿喝点水吧
The fountain is over there, Michelle. 饮水机在那 Michellle。
Near the Exit sign. 就在出口标 附近。
Thank you. 谢谢 。
Michelle is a little shy. Michelle有点不好意思思
I used to be that way when I was her age. 我像她这般年纪也是这这样
Harry, if Michelle doesn't want to go, Harry 如果Michelle膊 想去
we don't have to. 我们不必勉强。
She'll be fine. 她没有问题。
Remember, 别忘了
I haven't dated any one else since her mother died. 自从她母亲去世之後 我从没有和别人约会过。
This is a little difficult for her. 这对她来说有点不习惯惯
Are you ready to go? 准备好动身吗
Yes. But could you wait one minute? 是的。不过 你能等一一下
I have a call to make. 我需要打个电话
Would you excuse me? 失陪一下。
Sam, get Mr. Levine at Toytown Stores Sam 给Toytown Storees的Levine先生
on the telephone for me, please. 请替我拨电话。
Right. 好的。
Hello. Susan Stewart calling Mr. Levine, please. 喂 Susan Stewart想父鶯evine先生通话。
He's on the phone. 他在电话上。
Mr. Levine, Susan Stewart. Levine先生 我是Susaan Stewart。
I find myself in an embarrassing situation. 我现在有一件很糗的事事
I made another lunch date for today 我和别人约好共进午餐
and forgot to enter it in my appointment book. 但忘了写到工作日
Can you and I meet for drinks tomorrow? 你和我能否在明天见面面喝点什麽
I'd really appreciate it.... Yes.... Thank you.... 我非常感激……好的………谢谢你…
Tomorrow at five o'clock at the Biltmore. 明天五点钟 在Biltmoore饭店。
I'll see you then. 到时候见啦。
Thank you, Mr. Levine. 谢谢你 Levine先生。
鸣谢：宋涛涛 taotaosong@163.com QQ: 498783048
Welcome to the South Street restaurant, folks. 欢迎光临南街餐馆 各各位
What'll it be? 想来点什麽
What do you recommend? 你推 什麽
Well, the crab salad's always a big hit. 嗯 蟹肉沙拉一向是构 受欢迎的。
Susan, would you like the crab salad? Susan 要不要蟹肉缮忱
I'd love the crab salad. 我要蟹肉沙拉。
Michelle, would you like to try the crab salad, too? Michelle 要不要也也试试蟹肉沙
OK, Daddy. 好的 爸爸。
We'll have three crab salads 我们来三份蟹肉沙拉
and a pitcher of lemonade. 和一壶柠檬汁。
Help yourself to celery and carrots and other vegetables. 请你们自己盛芹菜 胡胡萝 和其他蔬菜
We used to catch crabs. 我们以前常捉螃蟹。
Where was that? 在什麽地方
We had a summer house on Fire Island. 我们在火岛有一所避暑暑别
Do you remember, Michelle? 你还记得吗 Michelle
Sure. 当然记得。
You and Mommy used to take me on the ferryboat. 你和妈妈常带我坐渡船船
Sometimes, at night, 有时候 在夜
we would go down to the beach and catch crabs, 我们走到海边抓螃蟹
remember? 记得吗
With a piece of meat on a string! 用一根绳子拴著一点肉
Right. 对。
Well, I think I'm going to go get us all some vegetables. 好啦 我想我去给大家家盛点蔬菜来
鸣谢：宋涛涛 taotaosong@163.com QQ: 498783048
There you go. 东西来了。
Thank you. 谢谢。
And some ice-cold lemonade. 还有冰凉的柠檬汁。
Enjoy it. 请享用。
Michelle, can I help you with the lemonade? Michelle 我帮 倒点点柠檬汁好
No, thank you. 不 谢谢 。
I'll wait for my father. 我要等我爸爸。
Michelle, can we have a talk? Michelle 我们能谈一一谈
Sure. 当然。
I know you miss your mother. 我知道 想念 妈妈。
You do? 真的知道
Yes. And I'm not trying to take her place. 是的 我 不想取代她她
Then why are you and Daddy 那为什麽 和爸爸
spending so much time together? 老是在一起呢
Because we like each other. 因为我们彼此喜欢。
And right now, he needs a friend. 而且现在 他需要一个个朋
I'm his friend. 我是他的朋友
I know you are. 我知道 是。
Sometimes he's very sad. 他有时很忧悒。
And so are you, I think. 我想 也如此。
Sometimes. 有时候。
I'd like to be your friend, too. 我也想成为 的朋友。
Will you let me be your friend, Michelle? 愿意让我成为 的朋朋友吗 Michell
So, what were you two talking about? 们俩刚才谈什麽了
Just girl talk, Daddy. 只是女孩子之间的谈话话 爸爸
It's too hard to explain. 这很难解释清楚。
You're probably right. 也许 说得对。
Well, let's get started. 好吧 我们开始吃吧。