Oh, it's a quarter to four, 噢 差十五分就四点了
and I have a production meeting at four. 我四点钟有个生产会议议
I planned to take you for a ride in Central Park 我原打算带 去中央公公
in a horse and carriage. 坐马车。
Harry, I'd love to, Harry 我确实想去
but I have work to do. 但我有工作要做。
OK. We'll walk back to your office with you. 好吧 我们陪 走回 的办公室去。
It's so nice out. 外面天气真好。
I decided to forget about my accounting problems 我已决定不再去想那些些会计上的问
and just enjoy this beautiful spring day. 尽情享受这美好的春天天
Take the time, Susan. 别那麽忙 Susan。
I know I should, 我知道应该这样
but ... well, there are too many things to do. 但是……我要做的事情情太多了
I understand. 我了解。
I'll go for a ride with Michelle. 我和Michelle一起去坐坐马车
Right. 好的。
Well, I had a really nice time. 嗯 我玩得很开心。
So did I. 我也一样。
I'm sorry you can't come with us, Susan. 很遗憾 不能同我们一一起去 Susan
So am I. 我也很遗憾。
Bye-bye. 再见。
Harry! Michelle!
Can you wait till I make a phone call? 哪 们等一下让我打个电话好吗
Sure. 当然。
鸣谢：宋涛涛 QQ：498783048 taotaosong@163.com
Susan Stewart's office. Susan Stewart办公室
Sam, this is Susan. Sam 我是Susan。
Hi. How was lunch? 嗨 午餐怎麽样
Fine. 很好。
You're late. 已经迟了。
The production department's waiting in the conference room. 生产部门的人正在会议议室等
I know. 我知道。
Ask Paul Smith to fill in for me. 叫Paul Smith代替我出出席
He knows everything about the production schedule, 他知道生产进度的一切切
and he can answer any questions. 他也可以回答任何问题题
Right. 好的。
Don't tell any one, 别告诉别人
but I'm taking a little time to smell the flowers. 我正利用一点时间轻 一下。
Good for you. 我真为 高兴。
It'll be our secret. 这只是 我之间的秘密密
But schedule another production meeting for tomorrow. 务必安排在明天举行另另一次生产会议
I'll be back 我会回来
for my six o'clock appointment with Mr. Ozawa. 参加六点钟与Ozawa先缮脑技
OK, Susan. 好的 Susan
And have a nice afternoon. 祝 下午玩得愉快。
Thanks. 谢谢。
鸣谢：宋涛涛 QQ：498783048 taotaosong@163.com
She likes you. 她喜欢 。
I know. I like her. 我知道。我喜欢她。
How'd you do it? 是如何办到的
We had a talk. 我们谈了一下。
About what? 谈什麽
Life. 生活。
And what did you decide? 那 们有什麽结论呢
That's a secret ... between us women. 这是个秘密……我们女女人的秘密