we need to have our own place to live. 我们应该有自己的的房子
Oh. 噢。
Well, what do you think about Richard and me 那麽 觉得我和和Richar
looking for a small house or an apartment 找一个小住宅或公公
at this point in our lives? 在这个时候怎麽样
We love having you here, 我们喜欢你们住这
and there is room, 这 有地方
and ... and when the baby comes, 而且……而且婴儿儿出生以
the baby can stay in your room for a while. 可以住在你们房间间一段时间
Richard feels we need to find a small house. Richard觉得我们行 要一个小住宅。
I remember when I was pregnant with Richard. 我记得当我怀著Riichard时
Philip and I were living with Grandma and Grandpa. Philip与我和爷爷爷 奶奶住在一起
Philip was a young doctor, Philip当时是个年年轻的大
and he kept talking about having a house of our own. 他老说要有自己的的家
It's natural. 这是很自然的。
What did you do? 那你们怎麽办呢
We looked at a lot of houses. 我们看了好多房子子
Did you find one? 找到合适的吗
Oh, not at first. 噢 没有马上找到到
We couldn't afford it. 我们当时不够钱。
Grandpa wanted to lend us the money to buy one, 爷爷要借给我们钱钱去买房
but Philip is too independent. 但是Philip的独立立性太强了
He didn't want to borrow any money. 他不想借钱。
Sounds like Richard. 听起来跟Richard乙 样。
They're all alike. 他们都是一个样子子
Richard is a real Stewart. Richard是个典型档腟tewart家後代。
He's independent, 他的独立性强
and sometimes just stubborn. 有时候甚至近乎顽顽固
When did you buy a house? 那你们在什麽时候候买房子
After Richard was born. 等生下Richard之後帷
I was teaching music, 我当时教音乐
and Philip was opening his first medical office. 而Philip则第一次次开诊所
Where was the house? 房子在什麽地方
Right here in Riverdale. 就在这 Riverddale。
Of course, it was a small house, 当然 那是一栋小小房
but just right for us. 但正好够我们住。
It's funny. History repeats itself. 真有意思。历史在在重演
Now Richard and I are having a baby, 现在 Richard和挝 有了孩子
and we probably won't be able to 而我们也许也一样样不
afford a house right away, either. 马上负担得起一栋栋房子
Why don't you look at some houses, Marilyn? 何不去看一看房房子呢 Marily
Good idea. 好主意。
Look in the real-estate section of Sunday's Times. 查一查星期天的 纽约时报 房地产版
You'll learn a lot. 会增长不少见识识
Maybe we should 也许我们应该
speak to a real-estate agent about a house. 和房地产仲介商谈谈一谈关於房子的事
And a bank about a mortgage. 还要和银行谈谈 睢
I'll talk to Richard about it. 我会与Richard商亮可 量。
I think it's a good idea, Ellen. 我觉得这是个好主主意 Ellen
We can learn a lot by asking. 我们到处问问会学学到不少东西
And if I can be of any help, 如果我能有所帮忙忙的
let me know. 告诉我。
As a matter of fact, 事实上
my friend Virginia Martinelli is a real-estate agent. 我的朋友Virginiaa Martinelli就是个房地产仲介。
Good. 好极了。
You won't believe this, 简直不会相信
but she sold us our first house and this one. 我们的第一栋房子子和这一栋都是她卖的
Well, I'll tell Richard, 嗯 我会告诉Richhard
and we'll go to see her. 我们会去找她。
Do you think the skirt length is right, Ellen? 觉得这裙子长度度合适
Do you think it's too long? 你会不会觉得太长长
I think the skirt is just right. 我觉得长度合适。
Are you planning to attach a train to it? 准备加拖地裙摆摆
No. No train. Just the dress. 不 不加裙摆。就就是这样连身套装
But I am going to make a headpiece of lace. 但我准备做一个蕾蕾丝头饰
That dress is gorgeous. 这套服装真华丽。
Thanks, Ellen. 谢谢 Ellen。
And thanks for the advice about the house. 也谢谢 关於房子子的建议
I'll talk to Richard about it 我就跟Richard商
the minute he comes home. 他一回来。
And remember, 记住
we love having you here. 我们喜欢你们住这这
There's no need to rush. 没有必要急急忙忙忙