There's nothing more joyous than the arrival of a new baby. 没有任何事能比新缮 儿的到来更令人喜悦的了。
I am so excited. Mother! 我好兴奋 妈妈
Just imagine--Marilyn and Richard must be thrilled! 想像得出 Marillyn和Richard一定乐坏了
Oh, a new baby! 噢 一个新生儿
Max ... Max ... Max. Max……Max……Maxx。
Oh, it's a sweet-sounding name for a sweet little boy. 噢 好一个甜美悦抖拿 配个甜美的小孩。
My first grandchild. 我的第一个孙子。
And my first nephew. 我的第一个侄子。
Isn't he just adorable? 他真是太可爱了
He looks a lot like you, Mom. He does. 他像 妈妈。他舷 。
Do you think so? 真的这麽认为
Well, I guess. He does look a lot like Richard, 嗯 有点像。他确适 很像Richard
and I guess he looks a lot like me. 我看也蛮像我。
Oh, he's got Richard's eyes, though. 噢 他的眼睛跟Ricchard的像极了。
I really want Harry and Michelle to see Max. 我真希望Harry和Miichelle来看看Max。
When are they coming? 他们什麽时候来
Tomorrow. Harry has an account to work on today. 明天。Harry今天有有项会计工作要做
Yes, he does have Richard's eyes. Big blue eyes. 是的 他的眼睛很舷馬ichard。蓝色大眼睛。
The baby even looks at you like Richard does. 这婴儿看 的时候乙蚕馬ichard那样。
Well, children usually resemble their parents. 嗯 孩子总是像父哪 的。
It's true. 对。
Michelle is a lot like Harry in so many ways. Michelle在许多方妹 很像Harry。
And she's shy with new people, just like he is. 她见了生人就害羞 与他一样。
You really like Michelle, don't you? 的确很喜欢Micheelle 是吗
Yes. I'm very fond of her. 是的。我很喜欢她
And Harry, too? 也喜欢Harry 是吗
Well ... 嗯……
Uh, it's four-thirty. Oh my! 啊 已经四点半了　０ 天啦
Marilyn and Richard will be home from the hospital any minute, Marilyn和Richard怂 时都会从医院回来
and we must prepare this room. 我们得收拾好房间
Where will we put all the presents? 我们把这些礼物放栽谀
Well, let's take everything to the living room. 嗯 我们把东西都贩诺 客厅去。
Marilyn and Richard and the baby need the space. Marilyn和Richard换 有婴儿需要空间。
It's crowded in here. 这 太挤了。
The welcome sign is up: 欢迎的标语已经弄 好了
"Welcome home, Max." 欢迎你回家来 MMax 。
Isn't it exciting, Grandpa? 真令人兴奋 是吗 爷爷
Your first great-grandchild. 你的第一个曾孙。
Yes. Yes, sir. 是的。是的。
A great-grandchild. A great-grandson. 一个曾孙。 一个曾曾孙
Another generation to carry on the Stewart name. 这是承继Stewart家家族香火的新一代
I love you, Grandpa. 我爱你 爷爷。
You make me feel so proud to be part of our family. 你让我以成为我们技 庭的一员而自豪。
One day, you'll have your own family, 总有一天 会有 自己的家
and I'll be proud to be part of it. 那时我会以成为 技业囊 份子而自豪。
Now you understand my feelings, Susan. 现在 能理解我的父 受了 Susan。
I'm Grandpa's daughter-in-law, but I feel like a Stewart. 我是 爷爷的儿媳父 但我觉得我是Stewart家的一员。
He's always made me feel like his own daughter. 他总是让我觉得我适 他的亲生女儿。
that's because you're so much like us--wonderful! 那是因为 太像我妹橇 太好了
Mom, got it. 妈妈 找到了。
This will make a nice gift for Marilyn and Richard. 这是给Richard和Maarilyn的一件好礼物。
They can keep a record of all of the important dates 他们可以记录下重乙 的日子
and information about Max's life here. 关於Max在这 的生生活
Let's see. 让我想想。
Name: Max Stewart. 姓名 Max Stewartt。
Does he have a middle name? 他有中间名字吗
No, just Max. I like that. 没有 就是Max。我我喜欢这样
No middle name. No middle initial. 没有中间的名字。妹挥兄 间的字母。
Like me. I'm Malcolm Stewart. 像我一样。我叫Mallcolm Stewart。
Just Malcolm Stewart. 就是Malcolm Stewaart。
And Max has your initials, Grandpa: M.S. Max的名字开头字母母与你的一样 爷爷 都是M.S.
Uh, it must mean something. 噢 这很有意思。
Weight: eight pounds six ounces. 体重 八磅六盎司
Eight-six. Big boy! 八磅六。是个大婴
All the Stewart men were big. Stewart 家的男人抖己 大。
Well, Robbie was eight pounds two ounces, 嗯 Robbie生下来鞍 磅二盎司
and Richard was eight pounds three. Richard生下来时八八磅三
And me? 我呢
Eight pounds six. 八磅六。
You were big, just like Max. 很大 像Max一样样
Eight pounds six, just like me. 八磅六 跟我一样
That's nice. Length. Length? 太好了。身高 多
Richard says Max is twenty-one inches long. Richard说Max是二适挥 长。
Twenty-one inches. 二十一英 。
Is that tall or average or what? 这样尺寸是高呢 换故 普通 或者算怎样
Tall. All the Stewart men are tall. 高 Stewart家的男男人都高
Well, Grandpa, you're about five-nine or five-ten. 嗯 爷爷。你大概 是五英 九或者五英 十。
I wouldn't call that tall. 我不觉得这样算高
I take after my mother's family. 我像我母亲家的人
They were ... they were ... they were average. 他们……他们……怂 们是普通身材。
Mother: Marilyn. Father: Richard. 母亲 Marilyn。父父亲 Richard
And lots of pages for Richard's photos of Max. 有好多页可用来贴RRichard给Max拍的照片。
Speaking of mother and of father 谈到孩子的爸 孩鬃 的妈
--and speaking of Max--I hear the car. 谈到小孩 挝 听见汽车声了。
They're here! 他们到了。
Oh! Oh, quickly! Go, go, go! 噢 噢 赶快 走 走 走
Let's see. Oh, welcome home. 让我看看。噢 欢佑 回家来。
Oh, let her in. 噢 让她进来。
Wait with your pictures for a second. 先别忙著你的摄影
Come on, darlings. 来 亲爱的。
Sweetheart .... Sit down right here. 心肝宝贝……就坐栽谡 。
Oh, he's so cute! Oh, Marilyn! 噢 他真逗人喜爱 噢 Marilyn
Max looks just like Grandpa. Max长得真像爷爷。
A real Stewart. 一个真正的Stewartt家後代。
I'm so happy to be home with my family--and with Max. 我真高兴回到家 汉痛蠹以谝黄 还有和Max在一起。