There's a conversation we have to finish. 我们有一段话话还没有谈完呢
What was it about? 刚才谈什麽
It was about caring. 谈到关心。
Oh? 噢
Yes, caring. 是的 关心。
I said that it makes me feel good 我是说我感到到很高
that you care about Michelle. 关心 Micheelle。
Well, I do care about Michelle. 是的 我真的的关心 Michelle
And it makes me feel good that you care about me. 而且 关心我我 也让我感到很高兴
You know I do. 你知道我是关关心
You're a ... wonderful friend. 你是个……极极好的朋友
And it makes me feel good 使我太高兴了
that you care about us. 关心我们大大家
Well ... well, 哦……哦
I do, Harry. 我是关心 HHarry。
It's only natural that if I care about Michelle 假如我关心 MMichelle
and I care about you, 也关心你
then I care about us. 那麽我便关心心我们大家
It's OK, Susan. 太好了 Sussan。
We had this part of the conversation 我们正谈到这这
before Michelle and her friends arrived. 在Michelle和和她的朋友们来之前
Now comes the good part. 现在最精彩的的部分来了
Like what? 什麽
Well, assume that if you care about Michelle 噢 假如你关关心 Michell
and you care about me 和我
and you care about us, 且关心我们们大
that we can talk about us. 我们就可以谈谈谈 我们
I mean--you and me. 我的意思是说说 和我
Isn't that right? 对不对
What are you trying to say, Harry? 你到底想说什什麽 Harr
What I'm trying to say ... 我想说……
since this is so easy .... 既然那麽简单单…
Here are ten letters that express my feelings for you. 这 有十个字字母可以表达我对 的感情
Don't be silly, Harry. 别闹了 Harrry。
You want a hint? 需要提示吗
It's two words. 两个字。
You're making the game harder. 你使 戏变难难了
Can't you figure it out? 找不到答案案
Seven letters ... two words ... 七个字母………两个字…
that express the feelings that I feel for you in my heart. 可以表达我内内心对 的感情
Harry, I get it! Harry 我想档搅
鸣谢： 宋涛涛 taotaosong@163.com QQ:498783048
Well? Does that mean you'll marry me? 噢 的意思思是 答应嫁给我
Is that a proposal, or are we just playing a game? 这是求婚呢 还是仅仅在玩 戏
Sit down, Susan. 坐下 Susann。
There's something I have to ask you. 我有一件事要要问
Susan, will you marry me? Susan 愿乙 嫁给我吗
It's such an important decision. 这是一个如此此重要的决定
There's so many things to talk about. 有许多事情需需要讨论
There are three things that have to be done first, Harry. 首先我们必须须做三件事 Harry
Three things? 三件事
First, we have to decide where to live. 首先 我们得得决定住在哪
Well, that's easy. 哦 那很简单单
We talked about that earlier. 我们先前谈过过这个问题
We'll live in New York. 我们会住在 NNew York。
All right. 好。
Second, 第二
we have to talk to Michelle together about being married. 我们必须一起起跟 Michelle谈谈我们结婚的事
We'll do that immediately. 我们可以立即即跟她谈
What's the third thing? 第三件事情是是什
You have to ask for my father's permission. 你必须徵得我我父亲的同意
Absolutely! 那当然
But first things first. 但事有先後。
We have to go pick up Michelle. 我们得去接 MMichelle了。
Oh, I'm so happy, Harry! 噢 我太高兴兴了 Harr
Not as happy as I am. 我比 更高兴兴