... my slogan is "I care." ……我的口号是 我关关心
I care about people, not things. 我关心人 而不是东西西
Vote for me, Ellen Stewart. 请投我 Ellen Stewwart一票。
I care. 我关心。
How was it? 怎麽样
You were terrific! 真是太棒了
Can I see it? 我可以看吗
Sure. 当然可以。
Hello. My name is Ellen Stewart, 你们好 我叫Ellen Sttewart
and I'm running for the open seat on the school board. 我正在竞选联合校董会会的席次
My slogan is "I care." 我的口号是 我关心 。
What does the word care mean? 所谓 关心 是指什麽麽
... I care about people, not things. ……我关心人 而不是是东西
Vote for me, Ellen Stewart. 请投我 Ellen Stewwart一票。
I care. 我关心。
I like it, 我觉得不错。
but now what? 但下一步怎麽办
How can we possibly get it on so Riverdale 我们怎样才能让Riverddale的人
will see it and hear it? 看到和听到它呢
Leave it to me. 交给我来办吧。
... I mean that when I say "I care", ……我的意思是当我说说 我关心
I care about people, not things. 我关心的是人而不是东东西
Vote for me, Ellen Stewart. 请投我 Ellen Stewwart一票。
I care. 我关心。
What happened? 发生了什麽事
Mom is now on television 妈妈现在出现在电视
in every appliance store in Riverdale, 在Riverdale的每一家档 器行
except Hamlin's. Hamlin的店除外。
He's a Boswell voter. 他是Boswell的支持者
That's a brilliant idea, Richard! 这主意太棒了 Richar
You inherited your father's brains. 你继承了你父亲的好头头脑
We got our brains from you, Dad. 我们从你那儿继承了好好头脑 爸爸
And guess what? 你们猜怎麽著
I called channel five. 我打电话给了第五频道道
Their TV news is going to cover it. 他们的电视新闻将报导导这一消息
"Housewife campaigns in appliance stores." 家庭主妇在电器行 进行竞选活动 。
And I'll bet 我敢打赌
some magazine will pick up the story, too. 一些杂 也将刊登这项项消息
Mom, you're going to win! 妈妈 会赢的
I know it! 我知道
Hold it, Robbie! 停停 Robbie
Just cool down. 冷静一点。
I know we're getting some attention now, 我认为我们现在固然渐渐渐引起一些注
but in the end the voters will have to decide. 但最後却要由选民来决决定
You're gonna win. 会赢的。
Trust me! 相信我
In the hotly contested race 在这场激烈竞赛中
for the one seat on the Riverdale School Board, 争夺Riverdale联合校抖 会一个席次
Mrs. Ellen Stewart has taken an early lead. Ellen Stewart太太初膊 领先。
She's winning! 她赢了
Mom, you're winning! 妈妈 赢了Now returning to other local news ... 现在再报导其它地方新新闻
Now returning to other local news ... 现在再报导其它地方新新闻
Riverdale High School Riverdale高中
beat its rival Horace Mann in baseball today It's too soon to know for certain. 现在还太早 不知道确确切情... 在今天的棒球赛中打败败了对手Horace Mann队
It's too soon to know for certain. 现在还太早 不知道确确切情
You're ahead. 领先呢。
That's better than being behind. 这总比落後要好。
More sports after this. 广告後还有许多运动消消息
It's not over yet. 还没有完呢。
Let's just all calm down, 让我们全都冷静下来
and wait for the final results. 等待最後的结果。
Ellen, why don't you go out to the backyard Ellen 何不去院子
and get some fresh air? 呼吸一些新鲜空气呢
Thank you, Grandpa. 谢谢你 爷爷。
I need some. 我确实需要。
What happened? 怎麽样
You came very close, Ellen. 差了一点点 Ellen
You lost by only a hundred and twenty-one votes. 仅仅以一百二十一票票的些微差距输了
I lost. 我输了。
You tried, Mom. 尽力了 妈妈。
You lost by a very small number of votes. 输的票数非常少。
Only one hundred and twenty-one votes! 仅仅一百二十一票
I'm sorry, Mom. 我很难过 妈妈。
There just wasn't enough time. 实在是没有足够的时间间
Look, 看
you've made a very strong impression 已经留下了非常深刻刻的印
on our community. 给我们的社区。
You'll have another chance next election. 下次选举时 还有机会会
Hello. 你好。
Oh, yes, yes, Mr. Maxwell. 噢 是的 是的 Maxwwell先生。
Hello, Mr. Maxwell. 哈 Maxwell先生。
How are you? 好吗
I just called to tell you 我打电话是想告诉你
that you are very impressive. 给人们留下了深刻的的印象
You lost the election, 选举输了
but you won the attention of the residents of Riverdale, 但 引起了Riverdale档木用 的注目
of Boswell, and of me. 和Boswell和我的。
Well, thank you, Mr. Maxwell. 噢 谢谢你 Maxwell舷 生。
I appreciate your kind words. 我很感谢你好心的安 课俊
I needed that. 我正需要这个。
I hear Boswell 我听说Boswell
wants to appoint you to a special arts committee. 将任命 到一个特别艺艺术委员会
I'm sending over a reporter 我将派一位记者
in the morning to interview you. 在明天早晨来 访 。
You are? 是吗
I'm gonna do an article 我准备写一篇文章
on "Ellen Stewart--she cares." 叫做 Ellen Stewart 她关心 。
Maybe we'll all care now. 也许我们大家现在都关关心起来了
Good-bye. 再见。
Thank you-- 谢谢你。
and good-bye. 再见。
What was that about? 说些什麽
You were right, Philip. 你说对了 Philip。
I did make a difference in town. 我确实在镇上发挥了影影响力
And in this family. 也在这个家 。