It looks wrong. 看起来不对劲。
Hmmm. It is wrong. 嗯嗯。是不对劲。
Are they always that difficult to make? 领结这样难 吗
The truth is ... yes. 老实说……是很难难
I'll try again. 我再试一次。
At this rate, 照这种速度
the wedding will take place tomorrow. 婚礼只有明天举行行了
Not to worry. 别担心。
OK. Here we go. 好吧。我们重来。
I'm worried, Philip. 我很担心 Philipp。
What if we can't tie the tie? 如果我们 不好领领结怎麽
If we can't tie the tie, 假如我们 不好领领
then there can't be a wedding. 婚礼就不能举行了了
You'd better not make Harry 你最好别让Harry
any more nervous than he is. 更加紧张了。
Don't worry. 别担心
We'll figure a way. 我们会想法子的。
How're you doing, fellas? 你们怎麽样了 各各
Not so good, Grandpa. 情 不太好 爷爷爷
We can't get this bow tie tied. 我们 不好领结。
Nobody knows how to do it. 没有人会 。
Do you? 你会吗
No. I never could, either. 不会 我也一直都都不会
Well, you have your own tuxedo. 噢 你有自己的无尾服
How do you tie your bow tie? 你怎麽 领结的
Yeah, Grandpa, 对呀 爷爷。
I've seen you in it. 我曾见过你那身打打扮
You look great. 你看起来很神气。
How do you tie it? 你怎麽 的
I don't. 我没 。You don't? 你没
What do you mean? 你是什麽意思呀
I never could tie one of those ... 我从来就不会打那那一类的…
things ... bow ties. 玩意儿……领结。
I have always worn a clip-on bow tie. 我都是用夹上去的的领结
A clip-on? 用夹上去的
Of course. 对啊。
Now I remember. 现在我想起来了。
Yes, it's so easy. 没错 它真简便。
All you do is 你所要做的就是
clip it around under your collar. 将它夹在领子下方方
We all need one of those. 我们都需要一个这这样的领结
The tuxedo rental store. 礼服出租店。
Do you think they're open? 你们说现在还开门门
Should be. 应该是开的。
Sunday's their big day. 星期天是他们大生生意的日子
I'll call and find out. 我打电话问看看。
Well, if they're not, 噢 假如店不开的的
I'll lend you mine, Harry. 我把我的借给你 Harry。
You're the only one 你是我们当中唯一
who really needs to be wearing a tuxedo, 真正需要穿燕尾服服的anyway. 不管怎麽说。
Thanks, Grandpa. 谢谢你 爷爷。
I'm the father of the bride. 我是新娘的父亲。
I'm supposed to be worried about my daughter, 我原该为我的女儿儿担心才是
and here I am with 如今我却和
the man that's marrying my daughter-- 将要娶我女儿的人人在一
worrying about him. 为他操心。
Poor Harry. 可怜的Harry。
I know the feeling. 我知道这种感觉。
Wedding-day Jitters. 这叫婚礼紧张症。
Are they open? 店开著吗
We're in luck. 我们运气好。
They're open. 店开著。
And they have lots of clip-on bow ties. 而且他们有许多夹夹上去的领结
I'll bicycle down to the village and get them. 我骑脚踏车去镇上上拿
You'd better hurry, Robbie. 你最好快点 Robbbie。
There's lots of time. 时间多得很。
A little over two hours. 两个钟头多一点。
In two hours and fifteen minutes 再过两小时十五分分
I'll be married to Susan. 我就要和Susan结换 了。
And be a true member of the Stewart family. 也真正成了Stewarrt家庭中的一员。
Oh, you're a lucky guy, Harry. 噢 你是一个幸运运的 伙 Harry
Susan is one of the best women you'll ever find. Susan是你能找到鬃 好的女人之一。
She's just like her grandma. 她就像她的祖母一一样
Now, once you put the ring on Susan's finger, 现在 你一旦将戒戒指戴上Susan的手
you are one of us, Harry. 你就是我们家中的的一员了 Harry
And don't ever forget it. 永远别忘记这一点点
Ring? Ring? 戒指 戒指
Oh my! 噢 我的天
What did I do with the rings? 我把戒指放哪儿了
I put them in the pocket of my sports jacket. 我把它们放在我运运动夹克的口袋
No, 不对
I think you put them 我想你是放在
in your tuxedo jacket pocket. 礼服上衣口袋 。
Remember? 记得吗
Right. 对。
What did I do with the rings? 我把戒指放哪儿了
Didn't you give them to Richard? 你不是把它们交给给Richard了
He's your best man. 他是男傧相呀。
I remember. 我记起来了。
You gave them to Richard. 你交给了Richard
Oh, yeah. 噢 对了。
I remember now. 我现在想起来了。
You handed them to me. 你将它们给了我。
What did I do with them? 我把它们放在哪儿儿
I hope they aren't lost. 但愿没丢才好。
Oh, don't worry, Harry. 别担心 Harry。
They have to be here. 它们肯定就在这儿儿
I remember. 我想起来了。
I gave them to Robbie to hold 我把它们交给Robbbie拿
so I wouldn't lose them. 免得我弄丢了。
Where's Robbie? Robbie在哪儿
Relax, Harry. 不要紧张 Harry
Robbie went to pick up Robbie去拿
the clip-on bow ties. 夹上去的领结。
Oh, I forgot. 噢 我忘了。
What time is it? 现在是什麽时间了
It's still a little over two hours, Harry. 仍然还有两个多小小时 Harry
Just relax. 不用紧张。
What about the rings? 戒指怎麽办
I'm sure Robbie has them. 我确定在Robbie那那
No, no, Robbie doesn't have them. 不 不 Robbie没没有拿
He gave them to me to hold on to them 他给我戒指 要我我自己保
because he didn't want the responsibility of holding them. 因为他不想承担保保管它们的责任
I put them in my tuxedo-- 我将它们放在我礼礼服的口
but in the lapel pocket. 但是在胸前的口袋袋
That's a relief. 现在我放心了。
I was really worried. 刚才我真的很担心心
I'll hold on to them for you. 我为你保管吧。
The best man always keeps the rings. 男傧相总是保管戒戒指的
You're right. 你说的对。
You hold on to them so there won't be a problem later. 你来保管 免得等等一下又出问题了
Well, 好了
now, I think we'd better get dressed, fellas. 现在我们最好去穿穿好衣服 各位
All right! 好的
Robbie will bring the ties back. Robbie会拿领结回回来
Hey, leaving me? 嗨 丢下我啦
You'll be fine. 你不会有事的。
Try to take it easy. 放轻 点。
It'll all be over in two hours. 再两个小时就结束束了
Over? 结束
The wedding ceremony will be over. 婚礼会结束。
You'll be husband and wife. 你们就成为夫妻了了
I guess you're right. 说的也对。
Two hours from now. 从现在起还有两个个小时