Philip ... Ellen. Philip ... Ellenn。
Ah, Judge. 噢 法官。
How are you? 你好吗？How are you? 你好吗？Hello. 哈 。
I think it's time for the wedding to begin. 我想是婚礼可以开开始的时候了
All right, ladies and gentlemen. 好啦 女士们 先先生们
Please take your places. 请大家就座。
The wedding ceremony is about to begin. 婚礼就要开始了。
感谢 涛涛 提供字幕 QQ：498783048 MSN:songtaotao1986@hotmail.com
OK, Jane. Start the music. 好 Jane。音乐开开始
Dearly beloved, 敬爱的人们
we are gathered here today 我们今天聚集在这
to join this man and this woman in holy matrimony. 见证这位男士和这这位女士的神圣 槊恕
Do either of you have any reason 两位之中可有哪位位因为某项原
why you should not be legally joined in marriage? 不该合法结婚的
Is there anyone present who can show 在座可有人能提出
any just cause why these two people 任何正当理由说明明这两
should not be legally joined in marriage? 不该合法结婚的
Then, Harry Bennett, do you take Susan Stewart 那麽 Harry Bennnett 你愿意接受Susan Stewart
to be your lawful, wedded wife? 做你合法的妻子吗
I do. 我愿意。
And you, Susan Stewart, 那麽 Susan Sttewart
do you take Harry Bennett 愿意接受Harry bennett
to be your lawful, wedded husband? 为 合法的丈夫吗
I do. 我愿意。
The rings, please. 请戴戒指。
I have them, Harry. 在我这 Harry
感谢 涛涛 提供字幕 QQ：498783048 MSN:songtaotao1986@hotmail.com
By the power vested in me by the laws of the State of New York, 凭著纽约州法律赋赋予我的权
I now pronounce you husband and wife. 我现在宣 你们成成为夫妻
You may kiss the bride now, Harry. 你可以吻新娘了 Harry
感谢 涛涛 提供字幕 QQ：498783048 MSN:songtaotao1986@hotmail.com