I really like this one Susan. Do you? Susan 我真档 很喜欢这一件 呢
Turn around, Michelle. Let me see the back of it. 转过去一下 Michelle。让我看看它的背面。
I like it a lot. It fits well. 我非常喜欢。。它很合身
It doesn't need any alterations. We must've bought the right size. 不需作任何修修改。我们一定是买对了 叽纭
I like the color. She looks good in blue. 我喜欢这颜色色。她穿蓝色的很好看
I like blue, too, Daddy. 我也喜欢蓝色色的 爸爸
Try on the skirt and blouse outfit, Michelle-- 试试上衣和裙裙子的那一套吧 Michelle
the one that Daddy wanted you to wear. 爸爸要 穿的的那一套
OK. 好的。
Michelle has been a different kid since we've been married. 自从我们结婚婚之後 Michelle变成另一个人了
She's never been happier. 她从来没有像像现在这样快乐过
And I've never been happier, Harry. 我也从来没有有这样快乐过 Harry
I love her very much. She's been a joy. 我很爱她。她她是个讨人喜欢的孩子
We're very lucky, the three of us ... 我们非常幸运运 我们三个…
and becoming part of the Stewart family, too. 而且成为Stewwart家庭的一份子。
We couldn't ask for anything more, could we? 我们再没什麽麽可求的了 对
Well ... 嗯……
Well ...? Could we ask for anything more? 嗯…… 我们们还有什麽可求的
Well ... we ... 嗯……我们……
How do you like it, Daddy? 你觉得怎样 爸爸
It's my favorite outfit. 这是我喜欢的的那一套
It's good for every day. It will be good for school, Michelle. 这套衣服每天天都可以穿。它适合上学时穿 Michelle
I like it, too. I always like skirts that go like this. 我也喜欢它。。我一直喜欢能像这样飘动的裙子
Do you want to see the winter jacket on me, Susan? 想看看我穿穿上冬季的夹克怎样吗 Susa
Yes, I do. Change back into your jeans, 是的 我想看看看。换回 的牛仔
and put on the new winter jacket we bought today. 也把我们今天天买的冬季夹克穿上
OK. 好的。
What did you mean by "well ...?" 你说 嗯……… 的意思是什
You had something on your mind 你显然有话要要
when I said we couldn't ask for anything more. 在我说我们再再没什麽可求的了的时候
Is everything all right? 一切都好吗
Everything is fine, Michelle. 一切都好 Miichelle。
Let's take a look at the winter jacket. Come on over here, honey. 让我们看看冬冬季夹克。到这儿来 亲爱的
It's kind of warm. 它很暖和。
It is. That's why we bought it for you. 是的。这就是是我们买给 的原因
This will be a perfect jacket for the wintertime 这一件夹克就就很受
when it's very cold out. 冬天外面很冷冷的时候
But it's kind of small also. We must've bought the wrong size. 但它也有点小小了。我们一定买错了 叽纭
Looks like we should've bought a bigger one. 看来我们应该该买一件大些的
I guess we'll have to exchange it, too. 我想我们还得得去换一件
I'm sure the store has others. 我相信那家店店一定还有其它的尺寸
I look silly! It is too small! 我看来很滑稽稽 它太小
You're growing so fast, Michelle. 长得太快了了 Michelle
Can I take it off? I'm hot! 我可以脱掉吗吗 我好
Sure. Put it back in your room, and we'll hang everything up later. 当然。将它放放回 的房间 过一会儿我们来一件件 起来
Well, are you going to tell me what's on your mind, Harry? 好了 你要不不要告诉我你在想什麽 Harr
I have been offered a job with a major accounting company 有一家大会计计公司提供我一个工
in Los Angeles. 在Los Angelees。
Los Angeles? That's a big decision. Los Angeles 这可是个大决定。
I know. It will also affect you and your job, if we decide to go. 我知道。假如如我们决定去的话 也会影响到你和你的工
Wow! It sure will. But first tell me about the job, Harry. 喔 当然会。。但首先告诉我是什麽样的工作 Harry
If it's a good one, then we'll make it work for us. 假如它是个好好工作 我们就顺水推舟
I have a client in the garment business, on Seventh Avenue. 我有个客户在在Seventh Avenue从事成衣生意
I do his taxes every year. 我每年为他处处理税务
He has a big sales office in Los Angeles, 他在Los Angeeles有一个大的销售办事处
and the company in Los Angeles 而在Los Angeeles
that does his major accounting work 承办他主要会会计工作的那家公
is looking for an executive. And he recommended me. 正在物色一位位主管。他推荐了我
That's wonderful, Harry. 那太棒了 Haarry。
Yes, but it would mean that we'd have to move to L.A. 是的。但这意意味著我们必须搬到Los Angeles
What about the salary? 薪水怎麽样
The real discussion comes tomorrow. 明天才会正式式商谈
Susan, I don't plan to make any decisions Susan 我不创 算做决定
until I have a chance to talk with you about it. 除非我有机会会跟 谈过
I understand, Harry. 我了解 Harrry。
And I don't have to make a quick decision. 而且我也不需需很快下决定
They know that I'm married and that I have a family. 他们知道我结结婚了 有一个家
Well, there's a lot to think about. 噢 有许多事事需要考虑
If it's a good job, 假如它是个好好工
then I've got to do some thinking about 那麽我就必须须考虑考
my career opportunities in Los Angeles. 我在Los Angeeles的事业机会。
Is everything OK? 一切都好吗
Yes, honey. 是的 亲爱的的