I love my school. I have so many good friends there now. 我喜欢我的学学校。我现在有那麽多好朋友在那
I wouldn't miss a day even if I were really sick. 即使我真的病病了也不想错过一天
Come and sit down for a minute, Michelle. 过来坐一会儿儿 Michelle
I'd like to talk to you about something. 我想跟 谈一一件事
Something important. 一件重要的事事
What's wrong, Susan? 有什麽问题吗吗 Susa
Oh, there's nothing wrong, Michelle. 噢 没什麽 Michelle。
But your daddy and I are talking about something 但 爸爸和我我正在讨论一件
that I'd like your opinion about. 我需要 的意意见
I know. I heard you talking about it 我知道。我听听到 们谈论的那件事
the other night when I was trying on my new clothes. 也就是我试新新衣服的那天晚上
It's about moving to Los Angeles. 是关於搬家到到Los Angeles的事
You're right. How do you feel about it? 说对了。 觉得怎麽样
Well, I really wouldn't want to move, but ... 噢 我实在不不愿意搬家 但是…
But? 但是什麽
But if you and Daddy wanted to, 但是假如 和和爸爸想搬的
I guess you know what's best for the family and for me. 我猜想你们一一定知道怎样做对整个家庭和我是最有利的
That's very considerate of you, Michelle. 真会体谅别人人 Michelle
But what about your friends? 但 的朋友怎怎麽
I'd miss them a lot, 我会非常想念念他们
but I know what it feels like to miss someone. 但我知道想念念一个人是什麽样的滋味
Honey, we don't have to move 亲爱的 我们们将不搬
if you're not going to be happy about it. 假如 会因为为这种事而不快乐的话
Does Daddy want to move? 爸爸想要搬吗
I think so. He's going to tell us tonight about the job offer. 我想是这样。。他今天晚上会告诉我们关於那份工作的事
Well, how was everybody's day today? 喂 今天各位位过得怎麽
Michelle was chosen to do Michelle被挑挑选去
the school poster for the play this year. 今年学校话剧剧的海报
Congratulations, Michelle! That's something! 恭喜 Michhelle 太好了
And how was your day, Susan? 那 今天过得得怎麽样 Susa
I see you're in a good mood. 我看你心情很很好
Why don't you tell us about your day. 何不告诉我们们你这一天过得如
I met with Bill York. 我与Bill Yorrk会面了。
It's OK to talk about it, Harry. 这件事可以摊摊开来谈 Harry
Michelle knows all about it. Michelle已经经全知道了
Really? 真的
Really, Harry. 真的 Harry
Michelle and I have all kinds of feelings Michelle和我我感觉很
about leaving New York, the family, and friends. 对於离开纽约约 家人 朋友
But if you think you should take the job, we're behind you. 但如果你认为为你应该接受这份工作 我们支持你
What about Michelle's school? 那Michelle的的学校怎麽
We'll move after the school term. 我们等这学期期结束後再搬
What about her new friends? 那她的新朋友友
I'll make new friends wherever we are as long as we're together. 只要我们能在在一起 无论在哪儿我都能交到新朋友
We're a family, Harry. 我们是一家人人 Harry
Whatever you think is right for you is right for us. 你认为对你是是好的对我们来说也是好的
I am so touched. The two of you are really something. 我太感动了。。 们俩个真是了不起
We love you, Daddy. 我们爱你 爸爸爸
And I love you. 我也爱 们。
OK. Now, tell us about your talk with Mr. York. 好啦 现在告告诉我们你跟York先生的谈话吧
Did you take the job? 你接受了那份份工作
Nope. 没有。
What? 什麽
No? You didn't take it? 没有 你没有有接
No, I did not take the job. 对 我没有接接受那份工作
But, Daddy, I thought ... 但是 爸爸 我想……
Harry, you didn't turn it down because of me ... Harry 你拒 绝它该不是因为我……
Or me? 或者我
No, no. I turned it down because of me. 不 不。我因因为我自己而拒绝了它
How's that? 这是怎麽一回事
Well, I began to think about you and about Michelle, 噢 我开始想想到 和Michell
and then I asked myself, 然後我问自己
do I really want to work for the biggest company in the country? 我真的想替全全国最大的公司工作
And? 结果呢
And I don't. 我 不想这样样
I went into business for myself 我当初自己开开
because I like being my own boss. 是因为我喜欢欢自己当老板
I run my own company. I'm a big fish in a little pond. 我经营自己的的公司。我是一条小池 的大鱼
I'm not really sure I want to be a little fish in a big pond. 我不是真的很很确定我想成为一条大池 的小鱼
Oh, Daddy, does that mean we don't have to move? 噢 爸爸 你你的意思是我们不必搬家
That's right, sweetheart. 是的 宝贝。
Are you sure? 你确定
I couldn't be more sure, Susan. 我再确定不过过了 Susan
I'm glad if you are, Harry. 假如你很确定定 我就高兴 Harry
And besides, 更何
how could I live in Los Angeles 我怎麽能住在在Los Angele
when all my favorite people live here? 而所有我喜欢欢的人都在
Your favorite people? 你喜欢的人
Who's that? 谁呀
The Stewart family, of course. 当然是Stewarrt一家人。