Hi, Mom. 嗨 妈。
Hi, Robbie. 嗨 Robbie。
You're home from school early. 你今天从学校回来得早
Yeah, they're getting the assembly hall 是啊 他们在布置会馆大厅
ready for the graduation ceremony, 为毕业典礼做准备
so we all got to go home early. 所以我们都早回家。
Too noisy to study. 太吵了 书看不下去
Well, now that you're here, 嗯 既然你回来了
you can help me with dinner. 你就来帮我准备晚餐
I need those potatoes peeled and sliced. 那些马铃薯需要剥皮汉 切片。
Mom, give me a break. 妈 让我喘口气。
Alexandra's coming over to help me study for my math final Alexandra就要来帮我温习数学 准备期末考试
Well, in that case, 嗯 既然这样
you can wash the dishes and clean up after dinner. 你就在晚餐後洗盘子 收拾桌子。
Can I invite Alexandra to stay for dinner? 我可以请Alexandra留留下来吃晚餐
Of course. 当然可以。
Thanks, Mom. 谢谢 妈。
You and Alexandra 你和Alexandra
have become good friends, haven't you? 成了好朋友 不是吗
Yes. I like her. 是的 我喜欢她。
She's a terrific person. 她人很好。
I'm going to miss her 我会想念她
when she goes back to Greece. 她回去希腊时
Would you like to give her a little farewell party? 你要不要为她举行一父鲂⌒突端 派对
Mom, that would be terrific! 那太棒了 妈
Maybe we could make it a surprise. 也许我们可以让它变吵梢怀【病
Oh, I don't know. 噢 这个我就不知道览病
Surprise parties don't always work out. 惊喜派对 不是每次抖 成功的。
Well, we could tell her 嗯 我们可以告诉她
it's a graduation party for me. 这是为我毕业所办的排 对。
When Alexandra arrives, 等Alexandra到达时
we'll surprise her. 我们再让她惊喜一下
Well, I suppose that might work. 嗯 我想这样或许可乙 奏效。
I'd like to give her a nice going-away present. 我很想送给她一件好档 离别礼物。
Fine. 好啊。
There's only one problem. 只有一个问题。
What's that? 什麽问题
I'm broke. 我身无分文。
I should have saved some money. 我早该存些钱。
I'm sure Alexandra 我相信Alexandra
would be happy with something simple, Robbie. 会欣然接受简单的东挝 Robbie。
I know. 我知道。
But, well, 但是 嗯
I'd like to give her something nice 我想给她一件精 的抖
to remember me by. 让她看到东西就想到挝摇
Maybe I could borrow some money from you and Dad. 也许 和爸爸可以借挝乙 点钱。
It's all right with me 我没有问题
if it's all right with your dad. 假如你爸爸答应的话
Thanks, Mom. 谢谢 妈。
I'll talk to him. 我会去跟他谈谈。
Is he still in his office? 他还在办公室吗
I think so. 我想是的。
Thanks, Mom. 谢谢 妈。
Robbie! Good luck! Robbie 祝你好运
感谢 涛涛提供字幕 QQ：498783048
Here are the X-rays you wanted, Dr. Stewart. 这是你要的X光片 Sttewart医师。
Oh. Thank you, Molly. 噢 谢谢 Molly。
Now, let me check them. 现在 让我来看一看
感谢 涛涛提供字幕 QQ：498783048
What do you think? 你看怎麽样
I don't see any breaks or fractures. 我看不出有任何破裂 或骨折。
Well, well. Thank you, Molly. 还好 还好。谢谢
Thank you. 谢谢你。
感谢 涛涛提供字幕 QQ：498783048
Come in! 进来
Hi, Son. 嗨 儿子。
Hi, Dad. Am I interrupting you? 嗨 爸爸。我打搅了哪懵
No, no, no, no. 不 不 不 不。
What's up? 什麽事
Can we talk? 我们能谈谈吗
Sure. 当然可以。
I need some help. 我需要帮助。
Well, that's what fathers are for. 嗯 父亲们的功用正栽 於此。
Well, before I go to college, 嗯 在我进大学之前
I have the whole summer ... 我有一整个暑假可以览 用……
Yes ... 对呀……
And I'm planning to get a job for the summer.
我想在暑假打工。
And what sort of job?
哪一类的工作
I applied for a job as a lifeguard at the community pool. 我申请了社区游泳池档木 生员工作。
Sounds pretty good.
听起来不错。
Yes. I'll be earning pretty good money if I get it.
是的。假如我得到这工作的话,我可以赚不少钱。
But right now, I'm kind of short of cash.
但现在,我手头很紧
Who isn't? 有谁不紧
And my friend Alexandra is going back to Greece ... 我的朋友Alexandra就就要回希腊去了…
Nice girl. 好女孩。
We'll all miss her. 我们都会想念她的。
Mom says we can give her a going-away surprise party. 妈妈说我们可以给她揪 行一个让她惊喜的欢送派对。
Good idea. 好主意。
And I'd like to get her a nice gift ... 我还想给她一份精 览 物……
What'd you have in mind? 你心 有什麽腹案
Well, a wristwatch, 嗯 一个手
so she'll think of me when she looks at the time. 这样当她看 的时候揪突 想起我。
Nothing flashy or expensive. 不是什麽俗丽或贵的
Something simple--but a good one. 要简单的 但要精 。
Sounds fine, Robbie. 听起来不错 Robbie
Well, I saw a nice watch. 嗯 我已看中了一个汉 。
But I'll need a loan. 但我需要借钱。
If you could lend me the money, 假如你能借钱给我的
I could pay you back out of my lifeguard salary. 我可以从我当救生员档男剿 拿出来还你。
Well, I guess your mother and I can manage it. 嗯 我想你妈和我可乙 设法帮这个忙。
When do you need the money? 你什麽时候需要钱
Would tomorrow be OK? 明天可以吗
You've got it. 没问题。
Thanks, Dad. 谢谢 爸爸。
My pleasure, Son. 不客气 儿子。
Oh, and, Robbie ... 噢 还有 Robbie…
Yes? 什麽
You'll probably want the family car 你也许需要用家的车
so you can drive her home after the party. 在派对结束後送她回技摇
Could I? 我可以用吗
If you drive carefully. 只要你小心驾驶。
I will. Thanks, Dad. 我会小心的。谢谢你 爸爸。
My pleasure. 不客气。
You're OK, Dad. 你很好 爸爸。
You're not so bad yourself, Son. 你自己也不错 儿子