"Richard Stewart's show at the Carlson Gallery "Richard Stewaart在Carlson画廊展出的
is a collection of photographs 是选出的摄影作作
from his new book entitled Family Album, U.S.A. 从他的新书Famiily Album, U.S.A.
There is power and beauty in Mr. Stewart's work, Stewart先生的鬃髌分姓 现出力与美。
and his book 他的书
introduces us to a remarkable new talent." 让我们看到一位位卓越的新秀。
Oh, Richard, it's wonderful! 噢 Richard 烫 棒了
Congratulations! 恭喜你
Wow! I'm overwhelmed. 喔 我太感动了了
Ladies and gentlemen, 各位女士 各位位先
if I may have your attention for a moment, please? 我想 用你们一一点点时间 好
I hope you're all enjoying the exhibition. 我希望你们都喜喜欢这个展
I know that I am. 我知道我是很喜喜欢
And I would like to introduce the young man 现在我希望向大大家介绍这位年轻
who spent the last five years 用过去五年的时时
taking these remarkable pictures 来拍摄这些 出出作
and writing the background for Family Album,U.S.A.-- 为Family Albbum,U.S.A.撰写背景说明的年轻人
Mr. Richard Stewart. Richard Stewarrt先生。
感谢 涛涛 提供字幕 QQ：498783048
Hello. 你们好。
I want to thank all of you for coming here tonight. 我非常感谢你们们大家今天晚上的赏光
I'd like to thank Harvey Carlson 我非常感谢Harvvey Carlson
for his faith in my project. 对我工作计划的的信心
But most of all, 但最重要的
I would like to thank my family 我要感谢我的家家
for their love and support all through this adventure. 在这整个工作期期间给予我的爱和支持
Thank you. 谢谢各位。
感谢 涛涛 提供字幕 QQ：498783048
Oh, I'm glad that's over. 噢 我真高兴终终於结束了
Would you mind? 你们不介意吧
Oh, not at all. 噢 一点也不。
感谢 涛涛 提供字幕 QQ：498783048 MSN：songtaotao1986@163.com
Thanks. 谢谢。
Our pleasure. 非常荣幸。
Hope it wins a Pulitzer Prize. 希望它能得Puliitzer奖。
I'll settle for an "A" in my photography course. 我只要摄影课能能得"A"就满足了
Ah, Richard, Marilyn, I want you to meet John O'Neill. 啊 Richard MMarilyn 我向你们介绍John O'Neill。
Oh, how do you do? 噢 你好吗?
Nice to meet you. 很高兴见到你。
I've been looking forward to meeting your husband, Mrs. Stewart. 我一直希望能见见到 先生 Stewart太太
I'm really impressed by your show. 你的展览让我留留下了深刻的印象
Thank you. 谢谢。
In fact, I'd like your autograph. 事实上 我想要要你的签名
Oh, well, really ... 噢 哦 真的……
On a contract. 在一份合同上面面
What's this about, Harvey? 这是怎麽回事 Harvey
Mr. O'Neill is the publisher of several magazines. O'Neill先生是汉眉讣以 的发行人。
Of course. I've seen you on television. 当然。我在电视视上看见过你
Mr. O'Neill was so impressed with your work O'Neill先生被哪 的作品深深打动
that he wants to develop it into a magazine concept. 他想要将它加以以发展 使之成为一个杂 方面的构想
Well, that sounds very exciting, 嗯 听起来很令令人兴奋
but where would I fit into the plan? 但是我在这项计计划中怎麽定位
I'd like you to be the photo editor of the magazine. 我希望你能做杂杂 的摄影编辑
Oh, Richard, how exciting! 哦 Richard 汉 令人兴奋
It's a wonderful opportunity, Richard. 这是一个好机会会 Richard
Hold on. Wait a minute, please. 等等。请稍等一一下
What's the problem, Richard? 有什麽问题吗 Richard
The problem is that I'm a photographer, not an editor. 问题是我是一个个摄影师 不是一个编辑
I like what I do. 我喜欢我所做的的工作
In fact, I love what I do ... 事实上 我热爱爱我的工作…
which is going out with a camera and a roll of film 那就是带著照相相机和一卷底片出去
and seeing the wonder of humanity. 看众生奇景。
Now, I appreciate your offer, 因此 我感激你你的提议
but I've worked so hard on Family Album, U.S.A., 但是我一直为Faamily Album, U.S.A.辛勤工作
and I'm giving some thought to a new book on a different subject. 如今我又开始在在构想另一本不同题材的新书
I'm flattered, 你的厚爱使我受受宠若惊
but I enjoy taking pictures, and I want to continue doing that. 但我喜欢拍照片片 而且我要继续做这一行
Thank you, 谢谢你
but I'm happy being a photographer. 但我乐於当一名名摄影师
I understand, Richard. 我懂了 Richarrd。
Richard, I know your next book will be a success. Richard 我相行拍愕南乱 本书会成功。
Congratulations! 恭喜你
Thanks. 谢谢。
You're a real Stewart! 你真不愧是Stewwart家的人