Subtitles added by Hanson Hu
root@pythoner.work
Episode 10 - Smell the Flowers
Good morning, Susan.
Good morning, Sam.
What's the schedule today?
Ten o'clock,
telephone FAO Schwarz about the new twin baby dolls.
OK.
Telephone Mrs. Zaskey at the advertising agency.
I did that. Go on.
Eleven o'clock, approve the sketches for the toy spaceship.
Where are they?
Right here.
Did you look at them?
Yes, I did.
What do you think of the spaceship?
I think the kids will love it.
Would you show me the drawings, please?
Huh.
Now, what else is on the schedule today?
Well, at one o'clock
you have a lunch appointment with Mr. Levine,
the client from the Toytown Stores.
Where?
At Rossano's.
Hmm. Anything else?
At four o'clock,
you have a meeting with the production staff
in the conference room.
Make sure everybody is at that meeting.
Will do.
At six you're meeting, Mr. Ozawa.
Oh, yes. Are his models here?
They're in my office.
I'd like to see them.
Right.
What else?
Come on, Sam.
You work too hard, Susan.
When was your last day off?
Hmm. I can't remember.
You really ought to take some time off.
What for?
To enjoy the simple things in life...
I know, Sam.
Maybe soon.
To smell the flowers.
Oh, wait a minute. What's today's date?
Today is the twelfth. Why?
It seems to me I scheduled something else.
There's nothing else in the appointment book.
I'm sure I did.
Oh, well, I'll probably remember it later.
I hope it isn't important.
Hmm. It's probably nothing.
OK, let's get started.
Would you call Priscilla Smith at FAO Schwarz, please?
Right.
These are the models from the Japanese film maker.
Thank you. Just put them on my desk.
And the new drawings for the toy spaceship.
Wonderful.
That was fast.
We have a new artist.
She's very talented.
What time is it, anyway?
My watch stopped.
It's 11:30.
What time is my lunch date with Bill Levine?
One o'clock.
Remind me to leave at 12:45.
Did you remember your other appointment for today?
No,
but I have a feeling
it's going to be too late when I do remember.
Yes, Sam?
I just solved the mystery.
What did I forget?
You have some guests in the reception room.
What? Who?
Mr. Harry Bennett and his daughter.
I remember!
Oh... Harry!
I made a lunch date with him and his daughter weeks ago.
Is he a client?
He's a friend.
Well, he's here with his daughter to have lunch.
I met her at Thanksgiving,
and I promised to have lunch with both of them today.
Yes, indeed.
What are you going to do about your appointment
with Mr. Levine?
Any suggestions?
Oh!
Hi, Michelle.
Hello, Harry.
It's nice to see you again.
Hello.
Hi, Susan.
We have both been excited about seeing you
and having lunch with you today.
Michelle picked these flowers out for you.
Daddy, can we go soon?
We're going to go to lunch in a few minutes, honey.
But I'm thirsty.
OK. You go out and get a drink of water at the fountain.
The fountain is over there, Michelle.
Near the Exit sign.
Thank you.
Michelle is a little shy.
I used to be that way when I was her age.
Harry, if Michelle doesn't want to go,
we don't have to.
She'll be fine.
Remember,
I haven't dated any one else since her mother died.
This is a little difficult for her.
Are you ready to go?
Yes. But could you wait one minute?
I have a call to make.
Would you excuse me?
Sam, get Mr. Levine at Toytown Stores
on the telephone for me, please.
Right.
Hello. Susan Stewart calling Mr. Levine, please.
He's on the phone.
Mr. Levine, Susan Stewart.
I find myself in an embarrassing situation.
I made another lunch date for today
and forgot to enter it in my appointment book.
Can you and I meet for drinks tomorrow?
I'd really appreciate it... Yes... Thank you...
Tomorrow at five o'clock at the Biltmore.
I'll see you then.
Thank you, Mr. Levine.
Welcome to the South Street restaurant, folks.
What'll it be?
What do you recommend?
Well, the crab salad's always a big hit.
Susan, would you like the crab salad?
I'd love the crab salad.
Michelle, would you like to try the crab salad, too?
OK, Daddy.
We'll have three crab salads
and a pitcher of lemonade.
Help yourself to celery and carrots and other vegetables.
We used to catch crabs.
Where was that?
We had a summer house on Fire Island.
Do you remember, Michelle?
Sure.
You and Mommy used to take me on the ferryboat.
Sometimes, at night,
we would go down to the beach and catch crabs,
remember?
With a piece of meat on a string!
Right.
Well, I think I'm going to go get us all some vegetables.
There you go.
Thank you.
And some ice-cold lemonade.
Enjoy it.
Michelle, can I help you with the lemonade?
No, thank you.
I'll wait for my father.
Michelle, can we have a talk?
Sure.
I know you miss your mother.
You do?
Yes. And I'm not trying to take her place.
Then why are you and Daddy
spending so much time together?
Because we like each other.
And right now, he needs a friend.
I'm his friend.
I know you are.
Sometimes he's very sad.
And so are you, I think.
Sometimes.
I'd like to be your friend, too.
Will you let me be your friend, Michelle?
So, what were you two talking about?
Just girl talk, Daddy.
It's too hard to explain.
You're probably right.
Well, let's get started.
Oh, it's 3:45,
and I have a production meeting at four.
I planned to take you for a ride in Central Park
in a horse and carriage.
Harry, I'd love to,
but I have work to do.
OK. We'll walk back to your office with you.
It's so nice out.
I decided to forget about my accounting problems
and just enjoy this beautiful spring day.
Take the time, Susan.
I know I should,
but... well, there are too many things to do.
I understand.
I'll go for a ride with Michelle.
Right.
Well, I had a really nice time.
So did I.
I'm sorry you can't come with us, Susan.
So am I.
Bye-bye.
Harry! Michelle!
Can you wait till I make a phone call?
Sure.
Susan Stewart's office.
Sam, this is Susan.
Hi. How was lunch?
Fine.
You're late.
The production department's waiting in the conference room.
I know.
Ask Paul Smith to fill in for me.
He knows everything about the production schedule,
and he can answer any questions.
Right.
Don't tell any one,
but I'm taking a little time to smell the flowers.
Good for you.
It'll be our secret.
But schedule another production meeting for tomorrow.
I'll be back
for my six o'clock appointment with Mr. Ozawa.
OK, Susan.
And have a nice afternoon.
Thanks.
She likes you.
I know. I like her.
How'd you do it?
We had a talk.
About what?
Life.
And what did you decide?
That's a secret... between us women.