Subtitles added by Hanson Hu
root@pythoner.work
Episode 21 - A Big Fish in a Little Pond
I really like this one Susan. Do you?
Turn around, Michelle. Let me see the back of it.
I like it a lot. It fits well.
It doesn't need any alterations. We must've bought the right size.
I like the color. She looks good in blue.
I like blue, too, Daddy.
Try on the skirt and blouse outfit, Michelle.
The one that Daddy wanted you to wear.
OK.
Michelle has been a different kid since we've been married.
She's never been happier.
And I've never been happier, Harry.
I love her very much. She's been a joy.
We're very lucky, the three of us...
and becoming part of the Stewart family, too.
We couldn't ask for anything more, could we?
Well...
Well...? Could we ask for anything more?
Well... we...
How do you like it, Daddy?
It's my favorite outfit.
It's good for every day. It will be good for school, Michelle.
I like it, too. I always like skirts that go like this.
Do you want to see the winter jacket on me, Susan?
Yes, I do. Change back into your jeans,
and put on the new winter jacket we bought today.
OK.
What did you mean by "well"?
You had something on your mind
when I said we couldn't ask for anything more.
Is everything all right?
Everything is fine, Michelle.
Let's take a look at the winter jacket. Come on over here, honey.
It's kind of warm.
It is. That's why we bought it for you.
This will be a perfect jacket for the wintertime
when it's very cold out.
But it's kind of small also. We must've bought the wrong size.
Looks like we should've bought a bigger one.
I guess we'll have to exchange it, too.
I'm sure the store has others.
I look silly! It is too small!
You're growing so fast, Michelle.
Can I take it off? I'm hot!
Sure. Put it back in your room, and we'll hang everything up later.
Well, are you going to tell me what's on your mind, Harry?
I have been offered a job with a major accounting company
in Los Angeles.
Los Angeles? That's a big decision.
I know. It will also affect you and your job, if we decide to go.
Wow! It sure will. But first tell me about the job, Harry.
If it's a good one, then we'll make it work for us.
I have a client in the garment business, on Seventh Avenue.
I do his taxes every year.
He has a big sales office in Los Angeles,
and the company in Los Angeles
that does his major accounting work
is looking for an executive. And he recommended me.
That's wonderful, Harry.
Yes, but it would mean that we'd have to move to L.A.
What about the salary?
The real discussion comes tomorrow.
Susan, I don't plan to make any decisions
until I have a chance to talk with you about it.
I understand, Harry.
And I don't have to make a quick decision.
They know that I'm married and that I have a family.
Well, there's a lot to think about.
If it's a good job,
then I've got to do some thinking about
my career opportunities in Los Angeles.
Is everything OK?
Yes, honey.
Hello. Hello there.
Are you ready for lunch with your grandpa?
Oh! Hi, Grandpa. Yes, of course, I am, but my mind isn't.
What's the matter, Susan?
A real dilemma.
Does it have anything to do with you and Harry?
Yes, but I don't know where to start.
Maybe I can help. Tell me what it is, Susan.
Thanks, Grandpa. Please sit down.
Oh! Harry has been offered a job in Los Angeles.
Well, this is something to think about.
There are so many things to consider. There's Michelle.
I wonder if a move would be a bad thing for her. And my job.
I don't know if I can get a good job in Los Angeles.
And what about our family?
Can I tell you what I think?
Tell me.
I think that you're very successful
and that you have a fantastic reputation in the toy industry.
I think you could talk to Mr. Marchetta,
and I think
he could help you find a real good job in Los Angeles.
He was very helpful to me, remember?
I suppose I could call him.
But I'm not so sure that I want to leave New York,
you, and the rest of our family.
Well, I'm not going to kid you, Susan.
You know we'd all miss you.
But this should be your decision.
It's something that only you and Harry can work out.
If moving to L.A. is in Harry's best interest,
I have to do what I can do to support him.
In every marriage,
sacrifices have to be made by one partner from time to time.
And what about Michelle?
Well, what do you think?
I think Michelle is better off staying where she is.
What does she think?
I don't know for sure.
Well, you'll have to ask her.
I think I'm going to have a talk with Mr. Marchetta
and get his feelings about my leaving.
And about helping me find a job in Los Angeles.
Good idea.
I'll call him right now. No point in delaying.
Thanks, Grandpa.
Harry, it's the perfect job for you. You'll love it.
It's a big decision for me, Bill.
And I have to discuss it with my wife.
I don't know if it's right for her.
She'll love it. It's a once-in-a-lifetime offer, Harry.
OK. Tell it to me again.
The company is Craft and Craft,
the biggest accounting company in the country.
I know the company well. It's big.
The biggest.
Yeah, yeah. The biggest. When do I have to let you know?
Talk it over. Think it over. Let me know by the end of the week.
When would we have to move?
As soon as possible.
I also have my daughter to consider.
I don't want to interrupt her school year.
Let me know by the end of the week.
It's a great opportunity for you, Harry.
Believe me.
I know.
Craft and Craft is the biggest in the country.
Yeah, I know. The biggest.
I think Michelle is asleep now. Let's talk.
I met with Bill York today.
And I talked with Mr. Marchetta. Did York make the offer?
Yup. He asked me if I want the job.
That's exciting, Harry. What was it?
A vice-presidency
with the biggest accounting company in the country -
Craft and Craft.
Aren't you excited about that?
Sure I am. But there's so much more to consider.
I talked to Mr. Marchetta.
What did he say? Did you tell him about me?
Of course, Harry. I want what's best for you,
and I think I can get a good job
through Mr. Marchetta
in Los Angeles also.
You're kidding.
No, I'm not kidding.
I talked with him, and he understands completely.
He has a major toy buyer in Los Angeles,
and he's pretty sure that I can get a good job there.
Unbelievable!
But I think we should talk to Michelle about all of this.
You're right. We'll talk to her about it.
And how do you feel about taking the job in Los Angeles?
How should I feel?
It's the biggest company in the country.
Well, then you feel good about taking it?
Well... I feel fine about it. Why shouldn't I?
I love my school. I have so many good friends there now.
I wouldn't miss a day even if I were really sick.
Come and sit down for a minute, Michelle.
I'd like to talk to you about something.
Something important.
What's wrong, Susan?
Oh, there's nothing wrong, Michelle.
But your daddy and I are talking about something
that I'd like your opinion about.
I know. I heard you talking about it
the other night when I was trying on my new clothes.
It's about moving to Los Angeles.
You're right. How do you feel about it?
Well, I really wouldn't want to move, but...
But?
But if you and Daddy wanted to,
I guess you know what's best for the family and for me.
That's very considerate of you, Michelle.
But what about your friends?
I'd miss them a lot,
but I know what it feels like to miss someone.
Honey, we don't have to move
if you're not going to be happy about it.
Does Daddy want to move?
I think so. He's going to tell us tonight about the job offer.
Well, how was everybody's day today?
Michelle was chosen to do Michelle
the school poster for the play this year.
Congratulations, Michelle! That's something!
And how was your day, Susan?
I see you're in a good mood.
Why don't you tell us about your day.
I met with Bill York.
It's OK to talk about it, Harry.
Michelle knows all about it. Michelle
Really?
Really, Harry.
Michelle and I have all kinds of feelings
about leaving New York, the family, and friends.
But if you think you should take the job, we're behind you.
What about Michelle's school?
We'll move after the school term.
What about her new friends?
I'll make new friends wherever we are as long as we're together.
We're a family, Harry.
Whatever you think is right for you is right for us.
I am so touched. The two of you are really something.
We love you, Daddy.
And I love you.
OK. Now, tell us about your talk with Mr. York.
Did you take the job?
Nope.
What?
No? You didn't take it?
No, I did not take the job.
But, Daddy, I thought ...
Harry, you didn't turn it down because of me... Harry
Or me?
No, no. I turned it down because of me.
How's that?
Well, I began to think about you and about Michelle,
and then I asked myself,
do I really want to work for the biggest company in the country?
And?
And I don't.
I went into business for myself
because I like being my own boss.
I run my own company. I'm a big fish in a little pond.
I'm not really sure I want to be a little fish in a big pond.
Oh, Daddy, does that mean we don't have to move?
That's right, sweetheart.
Are you sure?
I couldn't be more sure, Susan.
I'm glad if you are, Harry.
And besides,
how could I live in Los Angeles
when all my favorite people live here?
Your favorite people?
Who's that?
The Stewart family, of course.