Subtitles added by Hanson Hu
root@pythoner.work
Episode 22 - Career Choices
"Rock-a-bye, baby, on the tree top,
When the wind blows,
The cradle will rock.
When the bough breaks,
The cradle will fall,
And down will come baby,
Cradle and all."
Hi, Marilyn,
What are you doing?
Just sketching.
I've been thinking a lot about our responsibilities
in the past few weeks.
I never stop thinking about them.
I've been wrestling
with the question of whether I go back to work or not.
I see.
And I'm torn.
I really want to go back to work,
use my talents,
and pursue my career in fashion design
like we always thought I would.
But now...
I want to be with Max as a full-time mother,
especially when he's a baby.
I really understand, Marilyn.
But you never have to worry about Max.
There's Mother and Grandpa...
and I can always arrange my photo schedule
around your schedule,
if that will help.
It's not the same, Richard.
Have you discussed going back to work with your boss?
Rita Mae called yesterday. Rita Mae
Ah! That's what's got you thinking, isn't it?
She wants to know
when I think I'll be returning to the boutique.
And you said...?
I said I'd give her an answer in a few days ...
that I wasn't sure.
I'm sure Rita Mae will understand
and wait until you're ready to go back to work.
Well, maybe she will, and maybe she won't.
Who knows?
If I don't accept her offer,
maybe she'll find someone else in the meantime,
and when I'm ready to go back,
there won't be a job for me.
That's something to consider.
You've got yourself to think about, too.
But I am thinking about myself.
Don't you see?
What do you mean?
It's not just the job.
It's also my career as Max's mother.
That's the way I look at it.
I have two career opportunities at the same time.
My career as a fashion designer
and my career as a mother.
I never really thought about being a mother as a career.
I guess you do have two career opportunities
and a decision to make.
I hear Max.
I'll do it.
There's your teddy bear, Max.
He just loves that teddy bear
that Grandpa Philip bought for him.
I took him to Philip's office yesterday for a checkup.
You should have seen the look on his face
when Molly gave him the injection. Molly
Oh, did he cry?
No.
My dear little boy just looked up at me as if to say,
"Mama, what are they doing to me? Help!"
How did you feel?
Tell the truth.
Didn't you feel terrible?
I sure did.
I held him closely.
I kissed the top of his dear little head.
He looked up at me.
He tried to smile.
Being with him helped.
Helped him?
Or helped you?
Being a mother is not easy,
if that's what you mean.
Speaking of being a mother,
I've been meaning to ask you
what you were thinking about regarding going back to work.
I know Rita Mae called.
I can imagine what is going through your head.
I'm sure you can, Ellen.
There are so many things to consider.
One thing that makes it easier for you
is that you have us.
Max will always have a family member to watch over him
while you're at work.
I didn't have that when Richard and Susan were born.
What did you do?
I chose to continue with my career as a music teacher.
We hired a woman to watch Richard and then Susan,
and I continued with my career.
Do you think you made the right decision?
I think I did.
But when Robbie was born,
I decided to give full-time attention to raising Robbie.
I felt differently at that time.
And you gave up your career as a music teacher?
Not exactly.
I continued to teach piano lessons at home.
How did you feel about being away
when Susan and Richard were babies?
I think I did the right thing
for them and for myself and for Philip.
We needed the money.
Well, we do too, Ellen.
Everything I earn helps us towards getting that house
we want and need.
I can't wait till he's just a little older.
Our toy company makes the most wonderful toys for kids.
Max thanks you.
I thank you.
And Richard thanks you.
Now may I please say hello?
Hello.
I miss Max and think about him all week long.
We talk about him at dinnertime.
Will you please try to relax?
I've never seen you so wound up.
You seem to be enjoying the pressure.
The truth is, I am.
My job is not an easy one,
but I really enjoy it.
That is exactly what I wanted to talk to you about, Susan.
What's the problem?
Marilyn's career.
Well, my choice of careers.
Choice?
My career as a fashion designer
versus my career as a mother.
Why does it have to be one or the other?
That's what I said.
How's that?
Why can't you do both?
She's right.
Both?
Well, that's what I do.
I have a job, and I have Michelle.
I take care of both to the best of my ability.
It's not easy, but what is?
And that's what I did.
I did both with Richard and Susan,
and I did both with Robbie.
I thought you stayed home with Robbie?
I did.
But I was lucky enough to have a career as a music teacher
which I could continue at home.
Why can't you work at home, Marilyn?
You're very talented.
Designing dresses is a career
you could establish out of your home,
couldn't you?
I don't know why I didn't think of it.
It seems so simple now.
For a year or two
I could stay at home with Max and do my dress designs.
And you could make your dresses at home.
Sounds like a great way to solve the problem.
That could solve your problem, Marilyn.
I'm going to call Rita Mae at home
and ask her to come by and talk about it.
She wants to see Max, anyway.
I think that really answers your questions, Marilyn.
You can do it.
Do your designs at home - here.
And let Rita Mae do the selling at the boutique.
And you can both benefit financially.
I'm going to call Rita Mae right now.
Oh, Susan, thank you so much
for coming all this way from the city to talk to me about it.
I hope you don't mind
having taken so much time away from your busy schedule.
Are you kidding?
I don't mind at all.
As a matter of fact,
I came to spend some time with my favorite nephew.
I think you should call Rita Mae right now.
I think your idea of working at home is perfect.
I don't know what I would do without you.
I'm lucky to have you all.
We are lucky to have you, Marilyn.
And so is Max.
Hi, big guy.
That must be Rita Mae.
She sure got here quickly.
That's a good sign.
She must like you and your work, Marilyn.
I think she's just anxious to see Max.
She loves children.
Hi, Marilyn.
Welcome.
It's so nice of you to come.
Oh, I just wanted to see your baby, Max.
Hello, Rita Mae.
I haven't seen you since the hospital.
I'm Ellen Stewart, Marilyn's mother-in-law.
We met at the hospital.
How are you?
Oh, and there is Max!
Oh! My, how he's grown!
A little present for Max.
Oh, it's beautiful, Rita Mae!
You shouldn't have.
It's nothing.
It's just a little present for Max.
Can I get you some coffee or tea or a cold drink, Rita Mae?
Oh, nothing, thank you.
Well, I will leave you two to talk.
Come on, you big guy.
Yes, come on.
That's it.
It's nice seeing you.
Let me know if you need anything.
Thanks, Ellen.
OK, Marilyn.
You sounded like you've made a decision
when you called me.
I have made a decision, Rita Mae.
I've decided to stay at home and be a full-time mother.
I'm disappointed, but I respect your decision.
If I had a child as cute as Max,
I might do the same thing.
But I haven't finished telling you
the other half of my decision.
The other half?
Yes.
I think I can stay at home
and take care of Max and continue my career.
Sounds interesting.
Let me hear it.
Do you remember
our talks about custom-designed dresses for the boutique?
I sure do.
Why can't I design dresses for you here at home?
And make them here.
Have the fittings here, too.
And I could do the selling and the pricing at the boutique.
Exactly.
Oh!
What kind of dresses would you design?
I've thought about that for some time.
Yes?
Wedding dresses.
Wedding dresses?
Brilliant idea!
There's a big market today in wedding dresses.
That's what I thought.
I like the idea very much.
And if it's successful,
we can expand to all kinds of dresses.
That's what I thought.
As a matter of fact,
I have a customer for your first wedding dress.
My niece is getting married,
and I've been trying to find just the right thing for her.
Marilyn, you're going to design my niece's dress. Marilyn
That'll be our first one,
and then we'll use it to sell others.
Do you really mean it?
I really mean it.
It's a simple idea, and it will work.
You can certainly design dresses.
I know that.
And there's no reason why you can't do it from your home.
I'm so excited!
I can't wait to tell Richard!
If I had a baby like Max,
I'd want to stay home and be near him all the time, too.
You're making the right decision
for Max and for yourself too, Marilyn.
It all sounds so easy.
Now the hard work begins.
Would you like
to see some of my designs that I've been working on?
I'd love to.
Ooh! Oh, that's wonderful!
Ooh...