I am exhausted. My new exercise class is so hard. 我太累了。我哪切 的健身班太难了。
Your new exercise class? 的新健身班
Yeah. My new advanced exercise class. 对 新的高级浇 身班。
Why advanced? 为什麽是高级
My instructor thought that 老师认为
the beginner's class was too easy for me. 初级课程对我览此 太容易了。
Too easy for you? 对 太容易了
Don't laugh. In the beginner's class, 别笑。在初级靠纬讨
they give you a chance to rest between exercises. 你有机会休息
So? 那又怎麽样
The advanced class is nonstop. 高级课程 是妹挥行 息的。
I lift weights every morning for sixty minutes 每天早晨我举种 六十分钟
without stopping. 中间还不是没佑行 息。
No problem. 小事一桩。
Listen, Richard, 听著 Richard
doing aerobics for an hour is a lot different than lifting weights.一小时的有氧 运动可与举重大不相同。
Yeah. Quite a bit different. 是啊 相当不乙 样。
I think aerobics is easy. 我觉得有氧运抖 很容易。
I could work out in your class with no problem. 如果我去 的鞍 上做运动 一定不会觉得有问题。
You think so? 你这样认为
Oh, without a doubt. 啊 毫无问题
When's the next class? 下一次上课什鼢 时候
Tomorrow morning at ten o'clock. Try it. 明早上午十点　＠ 试一试吧。
Tomorrow morning after lifting weights, 明早举完重
I'll try aerobics. 我去试试有氧 运动。
It's a nap. Tomorrow morning at ten o'clock. 简单得很。明栽 十点。
Aren't you going to the aerobics class this morning? 今天上午你不适 去上有氧运动课吗
Of Course. Easy. No sweat. 当然 小事情　 绝无问题。
You are not going to be able to move 你会动都动不亮说
after this and the aerobics class. 在你做完这个 又去上有氧运动课之後。
Are you kidding me? 在取笑我
It's going to be a piece of cake. 这种事不费吹 灰之力。
You want to bet? 想打赌吗
Yeah. What's the bet? 好啊 赌什麽
I bet I can go one hour in your class this morning 我打赌我今天缮衔绲 的健身班运动一小时之後
and not feel a thing! 丝毫不累。
The bet is -- I win, and you cook dinner for the entire family. 这样赌好了
Or you win, and I cook dinner for the entire family. 要是你赢了 挝 替全家做晚餐。
It's a bet. 一言为定。
Ok. Call my instructor, Jack Davis, right now. 好 给我的老适Jack Davis打个电话 现在就打。
His number is 555-8842. 他的电话是5555-8842
The advanced class starts at ten o'clock. 高级健身课十档 钟开始。
Well, it's eight twenty now. 现在是八点二适 了。
It only takes eight minutes by bicycle to the aerobics class. 骑自行车去上佑 氧运动课只需要八分钟。
Give him a call. 打个电话给他
Davis Aerobics Center for Good Health. Davis有氧运动动健身中心
Jack Davis, please. 请找Jack Daviis。
This is Jack Davis. 我就是Jack Daavis。
Hello. This is Richard Stewart. 你好 我是Ricchard Stewart。
My wife, Marilyn Stewart, is a member of your program. 我太太Marily Stewart是你的学生。
I'd like to come to 我想
the ten o'clock advanced class this morning. 今早十点来上哪愕 高级健身班。
Oh, fine, fine. Be here a few minutes early. 啊 好 好。乔 早几分钟到这。
You need to complete some forms before the class. 上课之前你得烫 一些表格。
Thanks. I'm on my way over. 谢谢 我马上揪 来。
Good-bye. 再见。
Bye-bye. It's all set. I'm going. 再见。都安排汉 了。我现在就去。
Bye. 再见。
See you later. 待会见。
Good luck. 祝你好运。
Don't forget about the bet. 别忘了打赌的适隆
Dinner for the entire family. 给全家做晚餐
And that includes Susan. 包括Susan的。
Don't you forget. 你自己别忘了