Grandpa, Ellen, Philip, Robbie, you and me. 爷爷 Ellen Philip Robbie 你和我。
That's six steaks. 六份牛排。
Don't forget Susan. 别忘了Susan。
Seven steaks. 七份牛排。
Cooking dinner for the entire family is not so easy. 给全家人做晚膊 真不是件容易的事。
The shopping: the salad: 买项目 沙
tomatoes, lettuce, cucumbers, and onions. 蕃茄 莴苣 换乒 洋 。
The main course: steak and potatoes. 主菜 牛排和侣 铃薯。
Richard, how much broccoli do I need for seven people? Richard 七个个人吃需要多少花椰
Marilyn, I have to tell you something. Marilyn 我得得告
At today's exercise class... 今天上健身课档 时候……
Yes, Richard. 说吧 Richardd。
Well, I didn't really exercise. 嗯 我没有真档 上健身课。
I knew it! 我就知道
I wanted to, but Jack Davis needed a photographer. 我真的想参加缮峡 但Jack Davis要我拍照。
I'm sorry, Marilyn. 对不起 Marillyn。
I don't understand. Did you exercise or not? 我搞不懂 你档 底作了健身操没有
No. Instead of exercising, I photographed the class. 没有 没有 挝以 给他们拍照。
And you didn't exercise? 你没有参加健 身操
No. 没有。
There's another advanced class today at four o'clock. 今天下午四点种 还有一次高级班
We'll go together. 我们一起去。
What about the bet? 那打赌的事呢
Oh, the bet is still on, but you shop for the groceries. 打赌人仍然有行 但你去买菜。
Remember, you win, and I cook dinner for the entire family. 记得吗 你要适 赢了 我给全家做晚餐。
You win, and I cook dinner for the entire family. 赢了 我给热 做晚餐。
Including Susan. 包括Susan的。
Four o'clock at the advanced exercise class. With me. 四点钟去高级浇∩砜 跟我一起。
Don't forget to breathe. 别忘了呼吸。
Skip, hop, front. 跳 蹦 向前
Twist... again.... OK, now... scissors. 扭摆……再来　 …好现在……张腿合腿。
This is fun. It's a piece of cake. 有意思 毫不贩 力。
Yeah. Just wait. 是啊 等著瞧 吧。
5, 6, 7, go right, 1, 2, back, 5 6 7 向右右 1 2 後
2, 3 , 1, 2, 3, pony, pony... 2 3 1 2 33 小马步 小马步 ……
1, 2, 3, kick... 1, 2, 3, kick... pony. 1 2 3 踢 ……1 2 3踢……小马步
And twist, twist. 扭摆 扭摆。
OK. Let's pick up the pace. 好 把节奏加靠 一些。
How are you doing, Richard? 现在怎麽样 RRichard
I can barely move. 我简直动不了览病
2, 3, 4, front. Now we're going to run it off. 2 3 4 前踢踢。现在 我们来快跑
Front... knees up, knees up. 前踢 膝盖抬父摺
OK. Finish off by jogging in place. 好 结束之前栽 原地慢跑。
OK. Keep those knees up. 好 膝盖抬高
All right. That's it for today. 行了。今天就鬃 这些。
Thank you, everyone. See you next week. 谢谢大家。下行 期见。
Thank you, Jack, but no thank you. 谢谢你 Jack 但不谢 。
The advanced exercise class is not so easy, huh? 高级健身班不适 那麽容易吧 对不对
No, no, you were right. I was wrong. 确实不容易
Come on, Richard. Get up. Let's go. 好啦 Richardd。起来。走吧。
You have to cook dinner for the entire family. 你今晚得替全技易 晚餐呢。
Marilyn, I'm exhausted. I can't move. Marilyn 我太太累了。简直动不了
Oh, you'll do it. It's a piece of cake. 噢 你办得到档 。这不费吹灰之力。
Excuse me, Richard, Marilyn. 打扰一下 Ricchard Marilyn。
You are a terrific instructor, Jack. 你真是个了不破 的教练 Jack。
Thanks. But I have a question. 谢谢。但我想挝室幌
Is this your very first advanced aerobics class? 这是你第一次缮 有氧运动高级班吗
Yes, it is. 是的。
You are in great shape, Richard. 你的身体状 汉 极了 Richard。
Very few people last in this class 很少人能够
for the full hour the very first time. 第一次撑完一父 小时的课。
It's true. You are in great shape. 这是真的。你档 身体很好。
Thanks! 谢谢。
I think we'll cook dinner together. 我想 我们一破 做晚餐了。