OK. 喂
Do you know how to play charades? 你们会打哑谜吗
Frank, you've never played charades? Frank 你从来没没玩过哑
Nope. 没有。
Carl, you're sure you've never played? Carl 你肯定你创永 没玩过吗
OK, Betty, Tim, and Frank. 好 Betty Timm Frank
We're going to play charades. 我们来玩哑谜。
Frank, you can learn as we go. Frank 我们玩 你跟著学。
And, Carl, you join in at any time. 还有Carl 你随适 都可以加入。
OK, let me think. 好 让我想想。
OK, I've got one. 好 我有了。
All right. 行了。
A movie! 电影
Right. 对。
A movie. 电影。
OK. 好。
Six words. 六个字。
It has six words. 有六个字。
That's easy. 这很容易。
I can play. 我也能玩。
Good. OK. 好的。
We've got a movie. 我们知道是一部档缬
The title ... 名字……
Six words. 有六个字。
Right. 对。
First word ... 第一个字……
Sounds like. 声音像……
Sounds like ... 声音像……
You got that part right. 你们这一部份猜 对了。
Yes. 是的。
Sounds like ... 声音像……
Sounds like what? 声音像什麽
Sounds like no. 声音像 no 。
Absolutely right, Frank. 完全正确 Frankk。
OK. 好
We've got a movie. 我们知道是一部档缬啊
Six words. 六个字。
The first word sounds like no. 第一个字音像 nno 。
Row. Row. Row。 Row。
Go. Go。
Nope. 不对。
Show. Show。
That's it--show. 就是它 show　！　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　?
No ... OK ... 不是……好……
Snow. 雪。
Absolutely right, Betty. 完全正确 Bettyy。
Sounds like no -- snow. 音像 no 　snow”。
OK, a movie. Six words. 好 一部电影。亮 个字。
The first word is snow. 第一个字是 雪 。
This is fun. 很有意思。
Oh, OK. 噢 好了。
The fifth word. 第五个字。
Right, fifth word. 对 第五个字。
Seven? 七
Absolutely right. 完全正确。
Very good. 很好。
The fifth word is seven. 第五个字是七。
OK, we've got a movie. 好 我们知道有膊 电影。
The first word is snow. 第一个字是“snoow”。
Fifth word, seven. 第五个字是“sevven”。
I got it! 我知道了。
Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs. Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs〔白雪公主和七矮人〕
I got it. 我猜对了。
Frank, you got it. Frank 你猜对了了
Betty, you had it, but you didn't say it. Betty 知道答答案 但是 没有说出来
I knew it. 我也知道了 。
Carl, now you know charades. Carl 现在你知档 什麽是哑谜了。
Why don't you join us? 你何不参加入我妹堑 戏呢
I don't like charades. 我不喜欢哑谜。
It's for babies. 这是给婴儿玩的
Oh, I like it. 噢 我喜欢哑谜
Well, they're babies. 嗯 他们都是婴 儿。
You're a sore loser. 你是个输不起的热恕
Yeah. 对。
No arguing. 别争了。
Save your voices. 留著点嗓子。
Between now and tomorrow 从现在起到明天
you're all going to have your tonsils out. 你们都要切除扁 桃腺。
And you won't be able to speak for a while. 有一段时间 你妹敲 有办法讲话。
So save your voices till then. 所以 留著点嗓 子。
Hi, gang. Hi, everybody. 嗨 各位。
Well, what's going on? 噢 怎麽啦
I sure I am glad to see you, Dr. Stewart. 真高兴见到你来 Stewart大夫。
This is a rough group. 这是一群粗野的汉 子。
I didn't want to play charades, 我不想玩哑谜
so they're angry at me. 所以他们生我的破
Why don't you want to play? 你为什麽不玩
Because I don't want to be here. 因为我不想待在照 。
I don't want my tonsils out. 我不想切除 馓蚁腺。
Why not? 为什麽不想
Because my birthday is tomorrow. 因为明天是我的缮 日。
My mother promised me a birthday party with a clown. 我妈妈答应给我鞍 一个有小丑的生日派对。
But you can have one when you go home, Carl. 但你回去以後还靠梢 办一个呀 Carl。
But my birthday is tomorrow. 但是我的生日就栽 明天。
I'm sorry, Carl. 很抱歉 Carl。
Carl, you'll have your party when you go home, Carl 你回去以後 就可以开个生日派对了。
But it won't be on my birthday! 但那就不是在我缮 日那天了
And you promised me a surprise. 而且 答应给我乙 个惊喜。