Sam, would you come in, please? Sam 请进来一下 好吗
You sound like something's bothering you, Susan. 听起来好像 有什麽心适 Susan
The sketches for the cover of the new doll book? 是新玩具书的封面设计
That's not it. 不是这种事
Please sit down. 请坐下。
Sure. 好的。
I need your advice on a personsal matter, 我有件私事 需要听听哪愕 高见
but it's not about me. 但这不是关於我自己的适隆
You need my advice on a personal matter, 有私事需要听我的意
and it's not about you. 而且不是关於 自己的
It's about my grandfather. 是关於我爷爷。
What's the problem? 什麽事
It won't sound like a big deal, 这事听起来没啥严重
but it is. 但实际上很要紧。
I had dinner with him Saturday, 星期六我与他一起吃晚
and he's very unhappy about not working. 他对没有工作感到 筲蟛不乐。
I thought he was retired 我原以为他退休了
and pleased to be living with the family. 乐於跟家人住在一起。
He is, 没有错。
but there's so much energy and talent in the man, 但是他有那麽多的精力汉 才能
and he doesn't get to use it. 却又用不上。
But what can I do? 但我能帮什麽忙
What kind of advice are you looking for? 希望能得到什麽建议
Simply this. 简单说来是这样的。
John Marchetta runs this company. John Marchetta 经营这这家公司
He founded this company. 他创办了这家公司。
Right. 对。
John Marchetta gave me my start here six years ago, 六年前 John Marchettta让我在这 起步
When I first graduated from college. 那时我刚从大学毕业。
He gave me the chance to use my talents 他提供给我施展才能的换
and made me feel more confident. 使我对自己更加有信心
Right. 是的。
Maybe he can do the same thing for your grandfather. 也许他能为 爷爷做同蜒 的事。
Or at least give him some advice. 再不然至少可以给他一行 忠告。
Right. 对。
Then I've solved your problem. 说来我替 解决问题了
I can always depend on you, Sam. 我知道我可以依靠你
I'm glad to help. 我很乐意帮忙。
Shall I call Mr. Marchetta for you? 要我替 打电话给 Marcchetta先生吗
No, no. I'll do that. 不 不。我自己来
Thanks. 谢谢你。
Now, how's the Stewart family? 那麽 Stewart全家人抖己寐
Fine, thank you, Mr. Mrarchetta. 都好 谢谢你 Mrarchhetta先生。
Except for my grandfather. 除了我爷爷。
What's wrong, Susan? 怎麽啦 Susan
What's wrong with him? 他怎麽啦
He needs to work. 他需要工作。
In fact, that is the reason why I'm here to see you. 事实上 这是我来见你档脑 因。
I know you're building a new factory, 我知道你在兴建一座新构こ
and I thought ... maybe ... 我觉得……也许……
my grandfather is 我爷爷
so experienced in the construction trade, 在营造这一行业经验丰
he could be so valuable. 他或许能够有所用。
Tell him to come and see me 告诉他来见我
at ten o'clock tomorrow morning. 明天上午十点钟。
I have an idea that may solve the problem for him 我有个主意 也许能解揪 这个问题
and help a lot of other people. 且对其他很多人有益
Really, Mr. Marchetta? 真的吗 Marchetta先
Can I tell him that? 我可以把这消息告诉他
Sure can. 当然可以。
Ten o'clock in the morning. Here. 上午十点 在这 。
Oh, thank you! 噢 谢谢你