It's almost ten o'clock. 差不多十点了。
I've got to go. Tomorrow is Monday, 我得走了。明天是行 期一。
and work begins at eight in the morning for me. 早晨八点我就得开适 工作。
Oh, I'm so happy that Max is home. 噢 我真高兴Max回回到家了
He's the sweetest little thing. 他是最可爱的小 换铩
I'll drive you to the station, dear. 我开车送 到车站热ァ
You can catch the ten-twenty train to Grand Central Station. 能赶上开往Grandd Central Station的十点二十分班车。
I'll drive Susan, dear. 我送Susan 亲爱的的
Thank you, Philip. 谢谢你 Philip。
Then Grandpa, Robbie, 那麽爷爷 Robbie
and I can finish wrapping all these gifts. 和我可以把这些礼挝 包装完。
It's so good to have you home again ... 真高兴 又回家了
and to see Max asleep in his bassinet at home with us. 真高兴看到Max和我我们一起 睡在家 的摇篮
To be with our family and all that Stewart TLC. 真高兴和全家人在乙黄 受到Stewart家族无微不至的照顾
TLC--tender loving care. TLC 温暖的爱护护和关怀
That's our motto. 这是我们的格言。
Did you see the washcloth 你看见浴巾
and the towels with the teddy bears on them? 和泰迪熊毛巾吗
Alexandra and the Molinas sent them for Max. 那是Alexandra和 MMolina全家送给Max的。
It was so kind of them. 他们太客气了。
Now Max has come into everyone's life. 现在Max走进了每个个人的生活
The house is so alive with him here. 有了他在这 屋 头得生气蓬勃。
The welcome sign over the door. 门上的欢迎标语。
The boxes of presents. 那些礼物盒。
The M-A-X over his bassinet. 摇篮上的MAX字样。
Robbie put that there. 这是Robbie弄的。
Susan's teddy bear. Susan送的泰迪熊
So cuddly. The beautiful crib from Mom and Dad. 抱起来真舒服。爸鞍 妈妈送的漂亮婴儿床。
Oh, and Grandpa's baseball glove. 噢 还有爷爷的棒 球手套。
You know, it hung over my crib, too. 要知道 我的小床缮 也曾 过它。
And it hung over Robbie's crib. Robbie的小床也 构
Part of Grandpa's magic? 这是爷爷 魔法 档 一部分吗
Oh, that's not all. 噢 还没完呢
It hung over Susan's crib. Susan的小床也曾 过。
The same baseball glove? 同 一个棒球手套吗
That's right. Grandpa hangs it there for good luck. 是的。爷爷把它 栽谀 以求好运。
He says it always brought him good luck on the baseball team. 他说 当年他在棒乔蚨邮闭 手套总是带给他好运。
He believes it'll bring good luck to all the Stewart babies. 他相信这手套会给SStewart家所有的婴儿带来好运。
And then he takes it back 然後 他就把它收换厝
when Max is ready to use it? 当Max长大能使用这这手套时
Yes, 是的
and replaces it with a new glove 用一个新的手套来换凰
so the old one will be ready 这个旧的又可准备
for a new member of the Stewart family. 给Stewart家的新成成员了
Grandpa really loves his family, doesn't he? 爷爷确实很爱这个技 是吗
So do I. 我也一样。
And so do I. 我也一样。
And so does Max. Max也一样。
After he eats! 等他吃饱了