Thanks, Michelle. 谢谢 Michelle
I hope you like it. 希望 喜欢。
Isn't this baby outfit adorable? 这套婴儿装不是很靠 爱吗
With his name on it--"Max." 有他的名字在上面 “Ｍａｘ”。
Thanks so much, Harry and Michelle. 太感谢了 Harry和和Michelle
We really appreciate it. 我们实在很感激。
I'm glad you like it. 我很高兴你们喜欢
Michelle picked it out. 是Michelle选的。
Yes, I told Daddy to pick blue ones. 是的。我告诉爸爸蜒 蓝色的。
Blue is for boys, and pink is for girls. 蓝色是男孩子的 贩 红色是女孩子的。
And Max is some boy. Max是个好男孩。
He's a real Stewart. 他是个十足的Stewaart家的人。
Right. 对。
That was so thoughtful of you, Michelle. 想得真 到 Micchelle
Especially to pick it out in blue. 还特地选了一件蓝 色的。
Would you like to see baby Max, Michelle? 想看看Max小家伙伙吗 Michell
Could she? Could we? 她能看看吗 我们哪 看看吗
Could I? 我能看一看吗
Take them upstairs, Susan. 带他们上楼去 Sussan。
Harry and Michelle can watch Max sleeping. Harry和Michelle可可以去看Max在睡觉
Let's go. 我们走。
Come on, Michelle. 来吧 Michelle。
Before Max wakes up. 趁Max还没有醒来。
Will you please take this upstairs, Susan? 麻烦 把这个带上热 好吗 Susan
Uh-huh. 好 好。
Thank you. 谢谢 。
Michelle is very grown up for a ten-year-old, huh? 以一个十岁的孩子览此 Michelle很成熟 是吗
She's smart and sensitive for her age. 就这样的年龄来说 她很聪明而且懂事。
Growing up without a mother is difficult. 在没有母亲的情 舷 长大不简单。
You mature quickly. 这种人成熟得快。
Susan's like a mother to Michelle. Susan就像是Michellle的母亲。
They have a good relationship. 他们关 不错。
Do you think Susan and Harry will get married? 你觉得Susan和Harrry会结婚吗
Yeah. You can count on it. 当然 你等著瞧吧
I think so. Yes. They get along so well. 我也觉得是这样。适堑 他们相处得很好。
I like him. He's good for Susan. 我喜欢他。他很适汉Susan。
He's a little quiet. 他有点沉静。
It's hard to do anything but listen in this family. 在这个家庭 除亮 听别人之外还能怎样。
How can anybody get a word in around here? 在这 谁有机会膊 话呢
You're right, Ellen. 你说得对 Ellen。
Oh, really? 噢 是吗
It's the way it should be. 本该如此。
The Stewarts are the Stewarts! 这就是Stewart家人人的本
They always were, 他们过去如此
and they always will be. 将来也永远会如此
Right! 对
They've always got an opinion. 他们总有自己的看贩ā
Always got something to say. 总有话要说。
And now there's Max Stewart. 现在又加上Max Steewart。
and if he talks as loudly as he cries, 如果他说话像他哭乙 样大声
we're all in for trouble. 我们都会吃不消的
He's quiet now. 他现在很安静。
Mmm-hmm. That's because he's sleeping. 嗯。那是因为他睡亮恕
He's really cute. 他真是逗人喜爱。
It's not necessary to whisper, Harry. 没有必要压低声音怂祷 Harry。
A baby gets used to voices. 婴儿习惯各种声音
I remember now. 我现在记起来了。
We always whispered when Michelle was born. 当Michelle出生的适焙 我们总是压低嗓门说话。
And I didn't sleep well, Daddy told me. 而我总是睡不好。鞍职 告诉我的。
I never slept. 我总睡不著。
And when I did, 就算我睡著了
I woke up when I heard someone speak. 一听到有人说话我揪托 了。
I bet you were cute. 我打赌 当时很逗 人喜爱。
She sure was. 她小时候很逗人喜鞍
Not as cute as Max. 不如Max这麽逗人喜喜
He's like a little doll. 他像个小洋娃娃。
Oh, good. 噢 好了。
Now I can help diaper him. 我现在可以帮他换哪 布了。
Let's get Marilyn. 还是叫Marilyn来吧吧
What do you do when he cries like that? 像他哭得这个样子父 怎麽办
You pick him up. 把他抱起来呀。
He's so little ... so new. 他这麽小……这麽佑住
Let's call Marilyn. 我们还是叫Marilynn来吧。
Time for a feeding and time for a diapering. 该喂奶 换尿布的适 候了。
鸣谢：宋涛涛 taotaosong@163.com QQ:498783048
You're a real Stewart. 你是个真正的Stewaart家後代。