or the subway ... 或者搭地铁……
or a taxi. 或者坐计程车车
And there's so much to do. 而且这 总是是有许多事可做
Lots of movie houses, and the theater. 很多电影院 还有剧院。
I know what you mean. 我懂得 的意意思
I'd like to live in the city, 我也喜欢住在在
but living in New Jersey and the suburbs 但住在 New JJersey的郊区
is better for Michelle. 对 Michelle乙 好些。
Trees, grass. 有绿树 有草草地
There's a lot of good things about suburban living. 郊区生活是有有许多优点
I grew up in Riverdale, remember? 你记得吗 我我就是在 Riverdale长大
So I know. 所以我了解这这些
But, as a working woman, 但是就职业妇妇女来
I think New York has all the conveniences-- 我觉得纽约具具备了一切便利的条
including the best tomatoes. 包括上好的 蕃茄
The truth is, I'd like to live in the city. 老实说我也想想住到城 来
Michelle's the right age. Michelle正处处於成长的年龄
There are lots of things for her here. 这 有许多适适合她的东西
You're right, Harry. 你说的对 HHarry。
Today is the perfect example. 今天就是一个个很好的例子
Michelle and her friends are at the aquarium in Brooklyn. Michelle和她她的朋友们在参观 Brooklyn的水族馆
They come back here for lunch, 他们回到这儿儿来吃午
then go uptown to the Museum of Natural History. 然後再往北去去自然历史博物馆
There's so much for young people to see and do. 这 有很多可可供年轻人看和做的事情
It's just incredible! 简直是难以置置
Not just for young people. 不仅仅对年轻轻人来说是这样
What about me? 对我还不是一一
I've never been to the aquarium 我从来没有去去过水族
or the Museum of Natural History. Have you? 或自然历史博博物馆
Oh yes, Harry. 去过了 Harrry。
My mother and father 我父母
often took us somewhere in the city on the weekends. 经常在 末带带我们去城 的一些地方
Dad was a busy doctor, 爸爸是个很忙忙的医
but he usually managed to squeeze a Sunday in 但是他总会设设法挤出星期
with Richard, Robbie, and me. 和 Richard Robbie及我在一起。
I used to love to go to the Metropolitan Museum of Art. 我过去很喜欢欢去大都会美术馆
I've been there several times. 我到那儿去过过好几次
Twice with Michelle. 其中两次是和和 Michelle去的
You ought to think about spending more time with Michelle 你应当考虑多多花点时间陪 Michell
at all the great places in the city. 去城 所有的的好地方看看
Well, perhaps, 好的 也许
you'll help me select some of the great places. 能帮我挑一一些好地方
And perhaps, you'll join us? 也许 能跟我我们一起
Perhaps I will. 也许吧。
Well, there we are. 好了 就这样样了
All set for lunch, Harry. 午餐的一切都都准备好了 Harry
It looks inviting. 它看起来很令令人食指大动
I wish Michelle and her friends would get here. 我希望 Micheelle和她的朋友很快就到这 。
I'm starving, aren't you? 我饿了 呢
I can't wait to take a bite of the pumpernickel. 我简直迫不及及待想吃一口黑 包
It smells so delicious. 它闻起来好香香
Coming! Coming! 来了 来了。
Who is it? 是谁呀
Michelle. Michelle。
It's us, Susan. 是我们 Sussan。
Come in, Michelle, 请进 Micheelle
and bring your friends along. 请带 的朋友友们进来
We're on the fifth floor. 我们在五楼。
Oh, you've been here before. 噢 以前来来过的
Susan, Susan
I really appreciate 我真的很感谢
your doing this for Michelle and her friends. 为 Michellle和她的朋友所做的这些。
Oh, please, Harry. 噢 拜 你 Harry。
It's nothing. 这没什麽。
I'm not just doing it for Michelle. 我不仅是为 MMichelle做这些
I'm doing it for you. 也是为你做的的
Thank you. 谢谢 。
I'm doing it for us, Harry. 我是为我们大大家做的 Harry
Well, 是的
it's ... it's important for Michelle to see us together more often. 让 Michelle靠 到我们更常在一起是……是很重要的。
That's true. 确实是这样。
It's important 这是很重要的
for Michelle and me to get to know each other better. 让Michelle和和我彼此更了解
That's important for us. 这对我们很重重要
That makes me feel good. 那使我感到很很高兴
What, Harry? 什麽 Harry
What makes you feel good? 什麽使你感到到高
Well, that you care about Michelle, 哦 我是说你你关心 Michell
that you care about me, and 关心我 且
that you care about us. 关心我们大家家
Well, Harry, that's because I do. 哦 Harry 那是因为我关心。
I do care. 我真的关心。
They'll be here any minute. 他们马上就到到了
Susan, I'd like to continue this conversation later. Susan 我希希望等一下能继续我们的谈话
Of course, Harry. 当然可以 HHarry。
We'll finish the conversation when they go to the museum. 他们去博物馆馆之後我们再聊
I'd like that. 我很乐意。
So would I. 我也是。