Oh, Daddy! 噢 爸爸
We had such a good time at the aquarium. 我们在水族馆馆玩得真开心
I saw a real shark. 我看到一条真真正的鲨鱼
I could almost touch it. 我几乎可以摸摸到它
I'm so glad. 我真高兴。
Hi. Michelle, 嗨 Michell
why don't you introduce everybody to Susan? 何不将她们每每一位介绍给 Susa
Hi, Susan. 嗨 Susan。
I'd like you to meet Audrey and her mother, Mrs. Cooper. 我来向 介绍绍 Audrey和她母亲 Cooper太太
Hello, Audrey. 哈 Audreey。
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Cooper. 很高兴见到 Cooper太太。
I'm Susan Stewart. 我是 Susan SStewart。
And this is Shirley and Nicole. 这是 Shirleyy和 Nicole。
Hi, girls. 嗨 女孩们好好
Come on in. 请进。
Come on in, Mrs. Cooper. 请进 Coopeer太太。
Come on in, everybody. 大家请进来。
The aquarium was so exciting. 水族馆真的很很好玩
I had never been there before. 我以前从来没没有去过那
The girls learned a great deal. 女孩们学到了了许多东西
Frankly, so did I. 坦白说 我也也是
Well, please sit down 嗯 请坐下来
and tell us all about it during lunch. 一面吃午餐 一面告诉我们一切。
We prepared some tuna fish 我们准备了 埚塾
and cheese sandwiches for lunch. 和起士三明治治当午餐
I love tuna fish. 我喜欢吃鲔鱼鱼
Don't you, Audrey? 喜欢吗 AAudrey
I remember when I used to be a Girl Scout. 我记得我还是是一名女童子军的时候
My mother would take us everywhere, too. 我妈妈也是带带我们各处走
Susan, I understand you're in the toy business. Susan 听说 是在玩具业工作。
Yes, I am. 是的。
My company manufactures toys and games for children. 我们公司专为为孩子们生产玩具和 戏器具
Susan's vice-president in charge of new toys and games. Susan是主管行 玩具和新 戏器具的副总裁。
And the marketing of new toys and games. 还有新玩具和和新 戏器具的行销
Can we test a new game for you, Susan? 我们可以帮 试验 的新 戏吗 Susan
That's an excellent idea, Michelle. 这是个好主意意 Michelle
I happen to have 我这儿碰巧有有一
a game which I brought home to study. 我带回来研究究的 戏
Let us try it! 让我们试试吧
Do you want to play? 们想玩吗
Nicole? Shirley? Audrey? Nicole Shiirley Audrey
We tested it last week on twelve- to fifteen-year-olds, 我们上一 曾曾在十二岁至十五岁的孩子中试过这项
and they found it to be too easy-- 他们发现字太太简单
in other words ... boring. 也就是说
We think it might be just right for ten- to twelve-year-olds. 我们想它或许许对十岁到十二岁大的孩子正合适
That's us, Susan. 那正是我们 Susan。
First, you shuffle the deck 首先 得洗洗一下
and lay them face down. 将牌盖住。
Then you select the leader. 然後 们选出出指挥
I'll be the leader. 我来当指挥。
The leader takes the first ten cards 指挥拿出上面面的十张
and lays them face up on this stand. 将它们掀开放放在这个架子上
h-t-e-r-c-z-e-p-e-s. h-t-e-r-c-z--e-p-e-s。
Everyone gets a turn, going counterclockwise, 每一个人按逆逆时针方
left to right. 从左到右轮流流玩
You have thirty seconds to make a word, 们有三十秒秒的时间造一个
using as many letters as possible. 尽可能多用字字
You get one point for each letter, 一个字母可得得一分
plus the person with the longest word gets ten extra points. 所造的字最长长的人多得十分
The first one to get one hundred points wins. 首先达到一百百分的人赢
That's easy. 那太容易了。
OK, let's go around the table. 好 让我们顺顺著桌子来
You first, Audrey. 先来 Auddrey。
Chest--c-h-e-s-t. Chest c-h-ee-s-t。
Good. 好。
That's five points. 五分。
Next, Nicole. 下一位 Niccole。
Three--t-h-r-e-e. Three t-h--r-e-e。
OK. 好。
That's five points also. 也是五分。
It's your turn, Shirley. 轮到 了 SShirley。
Creep--c-r-e-e-p. Creep c-r--e-e-p。
Creep. Creep
That's another five-letter word. 又是五个字母母的字
Five points. 五分。
So far, you're all tied. 到现在为止 你们不分胜负。
Sheet--s-h-e-e-t. Sheet s-hh-e-e-t。
Sheet is a five-letter word. Sheet 是五个个字母的单字
Michelle, your turn. Michelle 父 了。
Cheese--c-h-e-e-s-e. Cheese c-h--e-e-s-e。
Terrific! 好极了
Michelle wins with a six-letter word, Michelle赢了了 她的单字有六个字
plus she gets an additional ten points 加上另外的十十
for a total of sixteen points. 她一共得十六六分
How are you enjoying the game so far? 到现在为止 们喜欢这个 戏吗
I think it's too easy. 我觉得它太简简单了
Too easy? 太简单
Michelle! Michelle
It's OK, Harry. 没关 Harrry。
Michelle is quite right. Michelle 非吵 对。
She just said it's too easy. 她仅仅说它太太容易了
Well, I like the game. 哦 我喜欢这这个 戏
I enjoyed lunch, Susan. 这顿午餐真好好 Susan
Thank you so much, 非常感谢 。
but we have to get going 但我们必须走走
to meet the rest of the troop at two o'clock at the museum. 我们得在两点点钟到博物馆与其他童子军会合
Oh, it was nice meeting all of you. 哦 很高兴会会见 们各位
I hope you have a wonderful time 希望 们玩得得开
at the Museum of Natural History. 在自然历史博博物馆
Good-bye, everybody. 各位再见。
Have a good time. 好好玩。
Bye. 再见。
See you in front of the museum at five o'clock. 五点钟博物馆馆前再见
Oh, OK. 噢 好的。
Thanks, Mr. Bennett. 谢谢 Benneett先生。
That'll be fine. 就这样说定了了
And thanks again for the lunch and for the game. 再次谢谢你们们提供了午餐和 戏
Good-bye, Susan. 再见 Susann。
It's not a bad game. 那不是个坏 戏
It's just ... slow. 只是……太慢慢了
Just slow. 只是太慢了。
You helped save our company a lot of money. 帮我们公司司节约了许多钱
Bye-bye. 再见。
You are wonderful with kids. 对小孩子有有一套
I am. 的确这样。
Isn't there a conversation that we have to finish? 我们不是有话话还没说完