You were right, Grandpa. 给你说对了 爷爷爷
Advertising, bills, bills, advertising. 广告 帐单 帐帐单 广告
Yes. It's just like I said, Robbie. 正像我说的那样样吧 Robbie
Nothing interesting. 没有什麽有趣的的
You won't believe it, Grandpa, 你绝不会相信 爷爷
but there's a letter here addressed to you, 这 确实有一封封信是寄给你的
Mr. Malcolm Stewart, and it looks like a personal letter. Malcolm Stewarrt先生收 而且看来是一封私人信件。
Oh, it must be a bill. 噢 还不是帐单单
I don't think so. 我想不是吧。
The return name and address is 发信人姓名和地地址
Pete Waters, RFD Number 1, Chesterton. Pete Waters CChesterton 乡村免费邮递路 一号。
You're joking. Pete Waters? 你在开玩笑吧。。Pete Water
Pete Waters, RFD Number 1, Chesterton. Pete Waters 舷 村免费邮递路 一号 Chesterton。
You know him? 你认识他吗
Do I know Pete Waters? 我可认识Pete Waters
You bet I do! 你可以打赌我当当然认识
He was my roommate in college. 他是我大学时的的室友
He visited with Grandma and me in Florida 他到Florida看构 祖母和我
about five years ago. 大约五年前。
What does he say? 他说了些什麽
Is he OK? 他还好吗
Yeah, he's fine. 是的 他不错。
Just fine. 相当不错。
He's writing to invite me 他写信邀请我
to spend a weekend with him at his farm. 去他的农场跟他他一起渡个 末
He's planning a get-together 他计划办一个 劬刍
with two or three other college friends. 邀两 三个其他他的大学朋友一起
A kind of a fifty-year anniversary reunion. 等於是五十 年年重逢聚会
Sounds like fun. 听起来好像蛮好好玩的
Fifty years? Wow! 五十年 喔
It sounds like fun to me, too, Robbie. 对我来说也像是是蛮好玩的 Robbie
What kind of farm does he have? 他的农场是什麽麽样
I've never been there, Robbie, 我从来没有去过过那儿 Robbi
but he has chickens and cows and all. 但他有 牛等等等
That means fresh eggs and fresh milk. 也就是说会有新新鲜的 蛋和牛奶
Does he have a family? 他有亲人吗
No, he doesn't, Robbie. 没有 他没有 Robbie。
He never married. 他没有结过婚。
He's not as lucky as I am 他不像我这样 倚以说
to have a family and grandchildren. 拥有一个家庭和和孙子们
I'm a lucky man. 我是个幸运的人人
How come he never got married? 为什麽他不结婚
That's a good question, Robbie. 这是个好问题 Robbie。
A very good question. 一个非常好的问问题
He never married because 他不结婚是因为
the girl he was in love with in college married someone else. 他大学时代所爱爱的女孩跟别人结婚了
As simple as that. 就这麽简单。
He never got over it. 他一直念念不忘忘
He must have loved her very much. 他一定非常非常常地爱她
Yes. Very much. 是的 非常爱。
Lillian Winters. 她是Lillian Wiinters。
She was in our class. 她和我们同班。
And what happened? 发生什麽事呢
She was in love with Donald McGrath, 她爱上了Donaldd McGrath
the quarterback on our football team. 我们足球队的四四分卫
Football players are always popular with the ladies. 足球队员往往很很讨女生的喜爱
She liked Pete, and they went to dances together. 她喜欢Pete 他他们也一起去跳舞
But her heart was with Donald. 但她的心 想的的是Donald
Did he ever get over it? 他有忘掉这件事事
No, he never did. 没有 从来没有有
Where is she today? 她如今在哪
I don't know. 我不知道。
Maybe Lillian will be at the reunion. 或许Lillian也会参加聚会。
You think so? 你想会吗
Pete's full of surprises. Pete总是出人意意表
I wish I could go there with you, Grandpa. 我真希望我能够够跟你一起去 爷爷
What do you think the surprise will be? 你想会是什麽样样的意外惊
With Pete, you never know, Robbie. 你不可能猜到Peete会耍什麽花样 Robbie。
Won't it be exciting to see all your college friends there again? 在那 又要见到到你的大学朋友 难道不兴奋
It is already. 现在已经很兴奋奋
I'm kind of excited about going now. 我现在就想去了了
Next weekend ... 下 末……
sleep over Friday and Saturday night 星期五和星期六晚上在那儿过
and come back Sunday. 然後在星期天回回来
I can't wait! 我迫不及待
Don't you think you ought to call Pete 你不觉得应该打打个电话给Pet
and tell him you're coming? 告诉他你要去吗
You're reading my mind, Robbie. 你说的正是我想想的 Robbie