Hello. Hello there. 哈 。哈 。。
Are you ready for lunch with your grandpa? 准备好跟 的祖父一起吃午饭
Oh! Hi, Grandpa. Yes, of course, I am, but my mind isn't. 噢 嗨 爷爷爷。是的 当然 我准备好了 但是有点心
What's the matter, Susan? 怎麽了 Susa
A real dilemma. 一个大伤脑筋筋的事
Does it have anything to do with you and Harry? 是关於 和Haarry的事吗
Yes, but I don't know where to start. 是的 但我不不知道从何说起
Maybe I can help. Tell me what it is, Susan. 也许我能帮忙忙。说给我听听 Susan
Thanks, Grandpa. Please sit down. 谢谢你 爷爷爷。请坐
Oh! Harry has been offered a job in Los Angeles. 噢 有人聘请请Harry到Los Angeles工作
Well, this is something to think about. 噢 这种事确确实需要想一想
There are so many things to consider. There's Michelle. 要考虑的事太太多了。首先是Michelle
I wonder if a move would be a bad thing for her. And my job. 我不知道搬家家对她来说是否是件坏事。还有我的工作
I don't know if I can get a good job in Los Angeles. 我不知道我能能否在Los Angeles找到好工作
And what about our family? 另外就是我们们家的人怎麽
Can I tell you what I think? 让我来告诉 我的想法好吗
Tell me. 告诉我吧。
I think that you're very successful 我认为你事业有成
and that you have a fantastic reputation in the toy industry. 而且在玩具界界有很好的声誉
I think you could talk to Mr. Marchetta, 我想 可以跟跟Marchetta先生谈
and I think 我觉得
he could help you find a real good job in Los Angeles. 他能够帮 在在Los Angeles找个很好的工作
He was very helpful to me, remember? 他帮过我大忙忙 记得
I suppose I could call him. 我想我可以打打电话给
But I'm not so sure that I want to leave New York, 但我不能确定定我真想离开纽
you, and the rest of our family. 你和我们家的的其他人
Well, I'm not going to kid you, Susan. 噢 我可不想想哄 Susan
You know we'd all miss you. 知道我们都都会思念
But this should be your decision. 但这必须由 做决定。
It's something that only you and Harry can work out. 这件事只有 和Harry才能定夺。
If moving to L.A. is in Harry's best interest, 假如搬到L.A..对Harry最有利的话
I have to do what I can do to support him. 我就应该尽我我的力量来支持他
In every marriage, 婚姻中
sacrifices have to be made by one partner from time to time. 总要有一方必必须不时做些 牲
And what about Michelle? 那Michelle怎怎麽
Well, what do you think? 嗯 觉得怎怎
I think Michelle is better off staying where she is. 我觉得Michellle待在原地比较好。
What does she think? 她怎麽想呢
I don't know for sure. 我不太清楚。
Well, you'll have to ask her. 噢 应当问问问她
I think I'm going to have a talk with Mr. Marchetta 我想我要跟Maarchetta先生谈谈
and get his feelings about my leaving. 徵求他关於我我离开的意见
And about helping me find a job in Los Angeles. 请他帮我在在Los Angeles找一份工作
Good idea. 好主意。
I'll call him right now. No point in delaying. 我现在就打给给他。没有道理要拖拉
Thanks, Grandpa. 谢谢你 爷爷爷
Harry, it's the perfect job for you. You'll love it. Harry 那是贩 最适合你的工作。你会喜欢的。
It's a big decision for me, Bill. 对我来说这是是个大决定 Bill
And I have to discuss it with my wife. 我必须跟我的的太太讨论
I don't know if it's right for her. 我不知道这事事对她是否恰当
She'll love it. It's a once-in-a-lifetime offer, Harry. 她也会喜欢的的。这是个千载难逢的机会 Harry
OK. Tell it to me again. 好吧 再说给给我听听
The company is Craft and Craft, 这家公司叫Crraft and Craft
the biggest accounting company in the country. 是全国最大的的会计公司
I know the company well. It's big. 这家公司我很很清楚。是大公司
The biggest. 最大的。
Yeah, yeah. The biggest. When do I have to let you know? 是的 是的 最大的。我什麽时候该给你回音
Talk it over. Think it over. Let me know by the end of the week. 好好地谈一谈谈。好好地想一想。这个 末以前让我知道你的决定
When would we have to move? 什麽时候我们们得搬
As soon as possible. 越快越好。
I also have my daughter to consider. 我还要考虑我我女儿
I don't want to interrupt her school year. 我不愿意打断断她这个学年
Let me know by the end of the week. 这个 末前给给我回音
It's a great opportunity for you, Harry. 这对你是个大大好机会 Harry
Believe me. 相信我。
I know. 我知道。
Craft and Craft is the biggest in the country. Craft and Crraft是全国最大的。
Yeah, I know. The biggest. 是的 我知道道。最大的
感谢 涛涛提供字幕 QQ：498783048
I think Michelle is asleep now. Let's talk. 我想Michellee现在睡著了。让我们谈谈吧。
I met with Bill York today. 今天我跟Billl York会面了。
And I talked with Mr. Marchetta. Did York make the offer? 我也和Marchrrtta先生谈了。York是否跟你谈那个工作机会
Yup. He asked me if I want the job. 是的。他问我我要不要接受那份工作
That's exciting, Harry. What was it? 太令人兴奋了了 Harry。是什麽样的工
A vice-presidency 副总裁
with the biggest accounting company in the country-- 全国最大的会会计公
Craft and Craft. Craft and Crraft。
Aren't you excited about that? 你不感到兴奋奋
Sure I am. But there's so much more to consider. 我当然兴奋。。但是还有那麽多问题需要考虑
I talked to Mr. Marchetta. 我跟Marchettta先生谈了。
What did he say? Did you tell him about me? 他怎麽说
Of course, Harry. I want what's best for you, 当然 Harry　Ｎ 要的是对你最有利的事
and I think I can get a good job 而且我想我也也可以找到一份好工
through Mr. Marchetta 透过Marchettta先生的帮助
in Los Angeles also. 在Los Angelees。
You're kidding. 在说笑吧。
No, I'm not kidding. 不 我不是说说笑
I talked with him, and he understands completely. 我与他谈了 他完全了解。
He has a major toy buyer in Los Angeles, 他在Los Angeeles有一个玩具大买主
and he's pretty sure that I can get a good job there. 他相当肯定我我可以在那儿弄到一份好工作
Unbelievable! 真不敢相信
But I think we should talk to Michelle about all of this. 但我认为我们们应该跟Micelle谈谈这整件事
You're right. We'll talk to her about it. 说得对。我我们要跟她谈谈
And how do you feel about taking the job in Los Angeles? 你对於到Los Angeles接受这份工作有何感想
How should I feel? 我该作何感想
It's the biggest company in the country. 它是全国最大大的
Well, then you feel good about taking it? 嗯 那你觉得得接受它很对
Well ... I feel fine about it. Why shouldn't I? 嗯……我觉得得不错。为什麽不