Hi, everyone. Sorry I'm late. 嗨 各位好。汉 抱歉我迟到了。
But Alexandra and I 但Alexandra和和
have been busy at work this morning 一早上都在忙
on the community-center project. 为社区中心的适隆
And we brought someone along who can help. 而且我们带来亮四 帮助我们的人。
You remember Charles Maxwell, Grandpa? 你记得Charless Maxwell吗 爷爷
He's the editor of the Riverdale paper. 他是Riverdalee报的编辑。
He wrote some nice articles on Mom 他写了一些介缮 妈妈的好文章
when she was running for the school board. 在妈妈竞选联汉闲 董会席次时。
Yes, I remember. You were a great help. 是的 我记得　 你帮了个大忙。
Hi, Mr. Stewart. 嗨 Stewart先先生
Hope to be a bigger help on the new community-center project. 希望能在新社乔 心这件事上提供更大的帮助。
From what Robbie and Alexandra have told me, 从Robbie和Aleexandra告诉我的情 看来
you people are making one big story. 你们正在 造乙 件大新闻。
Let me introduce you, Mr. Maxwell. 让我给你介绍 一下 Maxwell先生。
This is Nat Baker, 这是Nat Bake
who's responsible for this meeting, 他是这个会议档母 责人
and this is Joanne Thompson--and Abe Lucas, 这是Joanne Thhompson 还有Abe Lucas
who used to run the drugstore in town. 他过去在镇上揪 营药房。
Robbie and Alexandra told me Robbie和Alexaandra告诉我
what you need to fix up the old library. 你们修复旧图适 馆所需要的东西。
I am planning to write an editorial that I think will help you. 我计划写一篇缮缏 我认为应该能帮助你们。
Let's go. What are your questions? 我就进行吧。哪 想问哪些问题
OK. Now, I have ... first ... a couple of questions here. 好 现在 我佑小 …第一……几个问题。
Have you talked to the community council? 你们跟社区的乙 会谈过了吗
And have you had an engineer come in to do an inspection? 你们可有一个构 程师来做过检查吗
OK, what do you need most of all? 好 你们最需乙 的是什麽
People power. 人力。
Men and women, young and old, to give us their time. 不管男女老幼 请他们贡献时间。
To do what? 做什麽呢
To help scrub the building interior clean. 帮忙把建筑的哪 部擦洗乾 。
So that we can repaint it. 好让我们可以种匦 粉刷。
And you also need bodies to do repainting? 你们也需要人适 来重新粉刷吗
That's right. 是的。
And we'll also need some ladders 而且我们还需乙 一些梯子
and some brushes and some paint. 刷子和油漆。
When do you need the volunteers, 你们什麽时候行 要义工
and where do they report? 他们去哪儿报
I've got the council to agree 我已说服议会屯
to open the building for us on the next four weekends. 在往後四个 哪 开放那座建筑。
How about furnishings? 家具 摆设怎鼢岚
Are there any special requirements that I should list in the paper?有什麽特别的行 求要我列在报纸上的
Yes. 是的。
Here is a copy of all the things we need to start with. 这是我们一开适季 需要的所有东西的清单。
Let's see. Four desks. 我来看看。四照 桌子。
Eight straight-back chairs. Thirty folding chairs. 八张直背椅。热 十张摺 椅。
Six table lamps. Three end tables. One piano. 六个 灯。三照挪 。一 钢琴。
This is a good start. 这是一个好的靠 始。
These items shouldn't be difficult to come by 这些东西应该适 不难弄到的
once I print the article in the paper. 等我将这篇文照 刊登在报纸上。
This community has always been very generous. 这个社区一向适 非常慷慨的。
I agree, Mr. Maxwell. 我有同感 Maxxwell先生。
What you're saying is, in order for this center to succeed, 你刚才所说的乙馑际 为了使中心能成功
we need to put together volunteers 我们需要募集乙骞
from the various generations of future users. 从不同辈份的挝蠢 使用者中。
That's right. 是的。
And without their energy and stamina, 没有他们的体亮 和耐力
there's no way we can complete this project. 我们无法完成照 项计划。
I've got it. Now give me some information about 我知道了。现栽 告诉我
how you see the building being used. 你们计划如何适 用这栋建筑。
Oh, here. On the ground floor we have the reception area ... 噢 看这个。栽诼ハ 我们会有一个接待区……
It's here, Robbie. 就在这 Robbbie。
Charles Maxwell lived up to his word. Charles Maxweell 兑现了他的诺言。
"At the Stewart family home on Linden Street yesterday, “昨天在Lindeen街Stewart 的家中
a group of caring Riverdale citizens gathered 一群热心公益档Riverdale居民聚集在一起
to plan the refurbishing of the old library 计划重新整修览贤 书馆
to transform it into a new community center. 将它转变成一父 新的社区中心。
The original plan by the council 议会原有的计
was tabled because of lack of funds. 因为缺乏经费北 无限期地搁置。
The new plan needs you. 这项新计划需乙 你的协助。
You could call it a community unity plan. 你可以称它为缮 区团结计划。
It needs your time, and it needs your energy. 它需要你的时技 需要你的力气。
And it needs your contributions of furniture, 而且也需要你揪柘 家具
paint, brushes, ladders, lamps, et cetera. 油漆 刷子 烫葑 灯等等。
A list of these items and a volunteer form 这些物品的清档 和义工申请表格
can be picked up at the Riverdale Press offices. 可以到Riverdaale Press各办事处索取。
By working together, 透过共同工作
this community can do anything to benefit its citizens, 这个社区可做热 何造福居民的事情。
and we know you will all work together 我们相信各位换 共同出力
towards refurbishing the old library 去重新整修老屯际楣
and making it a new community center. 使它成为一个行 的社区中心。
Charles Maxwell, Editor." 编辑 Charless Maxwell。”