I'm so glad everyone is asleep. 很高兴大技 都睡了。
I thought Max would be crying, and everybody would be awake. 我还以为MMax会哭个不停 让大家都睡不著。
What did I tell you? 我不是告怂吖 吗
Nothing to worry about. 没有什麽汉 担心的。
I'm sure everything is fine. 我确信一乔卸 很好。
My mother knows all there is to know 我母亲完热 懂得
about taking care of babies, I assure you. 如何照顾行『 我向 保证。
Let's put some of this stuff away and then take off. 让我们把膊 份东西拿出来 然後就走啦。
We've got a forty-minute drive into the city. 我们还要靠 四十分钟 车到城 去。
Welcome home-- 欢迎归来
and I do mean welcome home. 我真心欢佑 你们回来。
Something wrong? 有什麽不抖 劲吗
Oh, nothing's wrong, Richard. 噢 没有适 麽事 Richard。
Believe me, Max is fine. 相信我 MMax很好。
But his teeth hurt, and he just can't get to sleep, poor dear. 但他的牙烫 他不能入睡 可怜的小宝贝。
Neither can you. 也不能热 睡。
Oh, I feel so bad. 噢 我真北歉
Oh, I'm fine. 噢 我很汉谩
How was your weekend? 你们的 哪┕得怎麽
We had a great time, Mom. 我们玩得贩浅 开心 妈。
It was wonderful. 太好了。
The weather couldn't have been better. 天气再好膊还 了。
It was nice here, too. 这儿也很汉谩
Did you get a chance to get outside at all? 有时间吵雒怕
Oh, yes. 噢 是的
Grandpa helped me yesterday afternoon. 昨天下午 祖父帮我的忙。
I went to the supermarket to get a few things, 我去一趟吵级市 买了几样东西
and I stayed out an extra half hour. 我还特别抖 待了半个小时。
The village was filled with people--the weather was so nice. 镇上挤满亮巳 天气好的缘故。
Harry's a professional camper, Mom. Harry是露露营专家 妈
He knows all there is to know, 他无所不
and he made the weekend very easy for us to enjoy. 使得我们档 末过得非常轻 愉快。
Come on. You all helped. 别这样说　 你们都帮了忙。
You were wonderful, Harry! 你真是了膊黄 Harry
Why don't you go to your room, Mom, and get some sleep. 为什麽不档 的房间去 妈妈 去睡一会儿。
Oh, I'm fine. 噢 我不乙 紧。
Tell me more about your weekend. 多告诉我乙 点你们的 末。
Did you do anything special? 你们做了适 麽特别的事情吗
Lots of special country things. 有许多特北鸬 乡村趣事。
We picked flowers. 我们 了换ā
And we brought some home for you. 而且带了乙 些回来给 。
It was so nice to be out in the country. 出去置身舷 下真是太好了。
They smell wonderful. 闻起来很舷恪
Everything smelled so special. 所有的东挝鞫加幸还商 别的味道。
It would have been great if we had been able to bottle the smells. 假如我们哪 将气味装瓶该有多好
It would be a great business if you could do that. 假如 能鞍 到那样的话 可是一笔大生意。
Oh! 噢
Uh, we're home now, Ellen. 噢 我们舷 在到家了 Ellen。
We'll take care of it. 我们去照构恕
I'll take care of it. 我来照顾
Let's see if it works. 让我们看靠词 不是有效果。
What's that? 那是什麽
A little special country music. 一点特殊档南 村音乐。
I think we'd better head home. 我想我们鬃 好上路回家啦。
It's getting late, and we have a bit of a drive. 已经晚了 而我们还要开好一段路呢。
Well, all your things are inside. 嗯 所有哪 们的东西都拿 来了。
There's your sleeping bag. 这是你们档 睡袋。
Oh, thanks, Harry. 噢 谢谢哪 Harry。
Say good-bye to Richard. 替我向Ricchard说声再见。
We'll call you all tomorrow night. 我们明天屯砩 打电话给你们。
Good-bye. 再见。
Bye, Mom. 再见 妈侣琛Bye-bye. 再见。
I'm so tired I think I'm overtired. 我好累 挝 想我是累过头了。
I don't know if I can get to sleep. 我不知道挝 能否睡得著。
Max has stopped crying. Max不哭了了
Yes. It works! 不错。有
It works! 有效
What works? 什麽有效
This. 这个。
Oh. Oh, where did you get that? 噢。噢 你们从哪儿弄来的
It sounds so nice. 很好听。
I think I'm falling asleep. 我想我要怂 著了。
Like Max did. 就像Max一一样
Good night. 晚安。Good night. 晚安。
Sounds of the country. 乡村音响
The soothing sounds of the country. 安详的乡 村音响。